<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Frank McPherson's Web Notes</title>
    <description>Follow &lt;a href=&quot;https://micro.blog/frankm&quot;&gt;@frankm on Micro.blog&lt;/a&gt;.</description>
    <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 21 Aug 2018 11:08:46 -0400</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 21 Aug 2018 11:08:46 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Google is releasing &lt;a href=&quot;https://techcrunch.com/2018/08/21/google-fit-gets-a-redesign-adds-heart-points-and-coaching/&quot;&gt;a new version of Google Fit&lt;/a&gt;. I use Google Fit to track my walking. My issues with it are less to do with the apps and more to do with the data.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is not obvious how to download your fitness data and Google doesn’t really provide much in the way of analyzing data. When looking at data like this you want to see trends so you can answer questions like, did I walk more than last week? Did I walk more than last month? Last year? Improvement is measured over time not in a point of time. It is shocking to me that a company that bills itself as data driven is does not provide much, if anything, for analyzing this data.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 21 Aug 2018 11:08:01 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/08/21/google-is-releasing.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/08/21/google-is-releasing.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bloomberg.com/graphics/2018-us-land-use/&quot;&gt;Here’s How America Uses Its Land&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I find the above article from Bloomberg fascinating, particularly that enough land is used to produce beer and Christmas trees to show up on the overall graphic.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 18 Aug 2018 16:45:34 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/08/18/heres-how-america.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/08/18/heres-how-america.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;While I faithfully use Google Calendar and Contacts, I seem to switch tasks apps after a few months. A few months ago I started using a new app and I’ve written &lt;a href=&quot;https://writing.frankmcpherson.net/ipad/2018/08/18/managing-tasks-with-noteplan.html&quot;&gt;an article about why I like Noteplan&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 18 Aug 2018 15:54:38 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/08/18/while-i-faithfully.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/08/18/while-i-faithfully.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;It’s Dream Cruise weekend in Detroit and it is always fun to see classic cars. Today I felt out of place witb out Terrain at the gas station.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://frankmcpherson.blog/uploads/2018/e7585136a5.jpg&quot; width=&quot;600&quot; height=&quot;600&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 18 Aug 2018 14:58:33 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/08/18/its-dream-cruise.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/08/18/its-dream-cruise.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;In my opinion, there is a problem with viewing the Internet as publicly owned. The Internet is corporate owned and has been for some time and corporations who own it are going to make decisions that are in their best interests.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;No part of the Internet is publicly owned, the last vestiges of that were given up when the FCC killed net neutrality.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If we truly want a free and open Internet we need to &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.vanityfair.com/news/2018/07/the-man-who-created-the-world-wide-web-has-some-regrets&quot;&gt;build a new one&lt;/a&gt; that is not controlled by corporations. &lt;a href=&quot;http://scripting.com/2018/08/16/132055.html&quot;&gt;You can talk all you want about how you want companies to act&lt;/a&gt;, but they will not act in the public’s best interests unless it just happens to coincided with their own interests.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yes, there are companies like Apple that give the impression they do make decisions in the public’s best interests, but I think Apple’s stances on privacy are self serving, it is their competitive differentiator.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can say much the same thing about the corporate owned media in the United States. The press that existed at the time the first amendment was written is different than how how it exists today.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There is little to no concept of “public square” today because nearly motive is driven by profit and no where enough motive is driven by public good.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 Aug 2018 16:35:48 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/08/16/in-my-opinion.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/08/16/in-my-opinion.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.lawfareblog.com/it-time-space-force&quot;&gt;Is It Time for a Space Force&lt;/a&gt;?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Answer: No!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Can you say, expanding &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.history.com/this-day-in-history/eisenhower-warns-of-military-industrial-complex&quot;&gt;military industrial complex&lt;/a&gt;? We can’t afford to provide health care to the citizens of this country because all our tax dollars are used to make suppliers to the military wealthy. When is the last time you heard of cuts to the defense budget?&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 Aug 2018 09:51:03 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/08/16/is-it-time.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/08/16/is-it-time.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.quantamagazine.org/universal-method-to-sort-complex-information-found-20180813/&quot;&gt;Universal Method to Sort Complex Information Found&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One thing I enjoyed when I was in college, studying computer science, were lectures on things like this that were way over my head.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What I really want to know is, is this a new way to determine &lt;a href=&quot;https://oracleofbacon.org/&quot;&gt;six degrees of Kevin Bacon&lt;/a&gt;?&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 Aug 2018 09:16:56 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/08/16/universal-method-to.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/08/16/universal-method-to.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;One thing I do not like about Android Pie is that it is not obvious how to uninstall apps. When you tap and hold an app icon in the drawer the uninstall option does not display until you move the icon towards the top.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 Aug 2018 09:01:20 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/08/16/one-thing-i.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/08/16/one-thing-i.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Does owning your own domain = owning your content? I am not so sure.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 Aug 2018 08:36:10 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/08/16/does-owning-your.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/08/16/does-owning-your.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.politico.com/magazine/amp/story/2018/08/14/americas-newspapers-just-played-right-into-trumps-hands-219360?utm_source=API+Need+to+Know+newsletter&amp;amp;utm_campaign=298c4fe52c-EMAIL_CAMPAIGN_2018_08_15_12_12&amp;amp;utm_medium=email&amp;amp;utm_term=0_e3bf78af04-298c4fe52c-34806089&amp;amp;__twitter_impression=true&quot;&gt;The plan&lt;/a&gt; by several newspapers across the country to all write editorials on the same day intended to rebut Trump’s claim that the press is the enemy of the people is a bad idea.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At the end of the day, the press needs to just do its job. One thing that I do think might be helpful is to point out that every president has issues with the press, they likely can produce past video of democrat and republican presidents taking issue with them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And here is the thing, in this context, &lt;strong&gt;the President of the United States is not “the people.”&lt;/strong&gt; Consequently, a press that does NOT explicitly agree with the President is NOT an enemy of the people, if anything they may be an enemy of the President.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Trump promotes the idea that he is just “one of us.” He, like all Presidents before him, is not just one of us.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The President serves us, and the Congress, the Supreme Court and yes, the Press, are the institutions identified by the founders of our country as being responsible to make sure the President serves faithfully by upholding his oath. By definition this means that when a person takes the oath of President of the United States, that person ceases being just one of us.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 15 Aug 2018 13:00:36 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/08/15/the-plan-by.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/08/15/the-plan-by.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://medium.com/taking-note/evernote-founders-impossible-mission-f769b5af8594&quot;&gt;On Preserving Human Memory: Evernote Founder’s Impossible Mission&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is always neat to read the story behind a favorite product. I am happy that Evernote has seemed to survive.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Aug 2018 18:27:41 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/08/14/on-preserving-human.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/08/14/on-preserving-human.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.poynter.org/news/200-newspapers-will-write-pro-journalism-editorials-will-they-also-listen&quot;&gt;This Poynter article&lt;/a&gt; makes so many good points, I wish everyone would read it. The worst thing that has happened  in the last 30 years is the general belief that it is wrong to change one’s mind, particularly if one is viewed as a leader. A real leader knows they always can learn, and therefore can always be wrong.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Aug 2018 17:16:29 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/08/14/this-poynter-article.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/08/14/this-poynter-article.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.poynter.org/news/200-newspapers-will-write-pro-journalism-editorials-will-they-also-listen&quot;&gt;Vanderbilt Chancellor Nicholas S. Zeppos&lt;/a&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;It is important for you to know what you believe, but it is more important for you to ask yourself regularly, “Why do I believe what I believe?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Aug 2018 17:10:51 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/08/14/vanderbilt-chancellor-nicholas.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/08/14/vanderbilt-chancellor-nicholas.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I am a long time user of Evernote, my first note was created in March 2008, but I have experience with that the original Windows app &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.fastcompany.com/90216018/inside-evernotes-brain&quot;&gt;described in this article&lt;/a&gt;. My main attraction to Evernote has been how its purpose aligns to how I view personal computing.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Aug 2018 13:04:48 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/08/14/i-am-a.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/08/14/i-am-a.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Most political decisions are being made based on emotions and not fact because emotion-based decision making has been taught to us by media ever since the first advertisement. The Internet is optimized for advertising and therefore emotion. And at the end of day, every opinion expressed on the Internet, including this one, is advertising.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Aug 2018 12:42:21 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/08/14/most-political-decisions.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/08/14/most-political-decisions.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I think &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.theverge.com/2018/8/10/17675232/twitter-alex-jones-jack-dorsey-free-speech&quot;&gt;the problem with articles like this one&lt;/a&gt; from the Verge about free speech and social networks is that they don’t get to the root cause, which are the conclusions and decisions people are making based on what they hear.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For example, there is no skepticism applied when one is telling another what they want to hear. When a politician holds a rally for their base, does anyone attending that rally ask themselves why the event is being held? What is the purpose? Is that I am being told true, or simply being said to earn my support.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Aug 2018 12:38:37 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/08/14/163837.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/08/14/163837.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;And &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.deadlinedetroit.com/articles/20418/new_yorker_magazine_the_fight_for_purity_in_michigan_and_the_democratic_party?utm_campaign=Feed%3A+DeadlineDetroit+%28Deadline+Detroit%29&amp;amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;amp;utm_source=feedburner&quot;&gt;here is why health care in the United States is a mess&lt;/a&gt;. I believe single-payer is the best method but most of the population in the United States has been convinced otherwise by the health industry, which will lose money under single payer.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Aug 2018 12:09:29 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/08/14/and-here-is.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/08/14/and-here-is.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I am re-thinking how I use tabs in my browser, and experimenting with the idea of only keeping one tab open at a time. Old school, but perhaps more focused.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Aug 2018 12:05:15 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/08/14/i-am-rethinking.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/08/14/i-am-rethinking.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cnet.com/how-to/google-location-tracking-turn-it-off-for-real/&quot;&gt;Pro tip&lt;/a&gt;: If you do not want your location tracked, do not have on your person something that contains a radio, like a smartphone. Otherwise, always assume that your whereabouts can be tracked.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;People managed to survive hundreds, neigh thousands, of years without carrying a smartphone every where they go. You can do it.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 14 Aug 2018 09:21:31 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/08/14/pro-tip-if.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/08/14/pro-tip-if.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <title>My Micro.blog Wish</title>
        
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I think of micro.blog as a publishing platform, for two reasons. First, what I write is published to &lt;a href=&quot;https://frankmcpherson.blog&quot;&gt;my blog&lt;/a&gt;. Second, what I write is published to other distribution channels, specifically for me &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/frankm&quot;&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/writtenbyfrank&quot;&gt;Facebook&lt;/a&gt;, but it could also include Medium and LinkedIn.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What would make micro.blog perfect for me is the ability to designate, at the time I am writing, to which distribution channels I want a particular item published to. All things that I write are appropriate for my blog, but some things I might only want to also be published to Twitter and yet other things I would prefer published to Facebook.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To me, the ability to control what gets published where, from the app in which I am writing, is particularly important if I were to publish to the LinkedIn and Medium channels that could be considered more “professional.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Right now, cross-posting is all or nothing. Everything I write in micro.blog is cross posted to Twitter and Facebook and frankly some posts, like this one, don’t make sense for those audiences.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I recognize there are drawbacks to cross posting, specifically, it’s a write once experience meaning that edits don’t get re-published to Twitter and Facebook because there just isn’t a mechanism to do so.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 13 Aug 2018 18:05:57 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/08/13/my-microblog-wish.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/08/13/my-microblog-wish.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Would you buy a smartphone specifically because it could also &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.theverge.com/2018/8/13/17675072/galaxy-note-smartphone-software-feature-history-computer&quot;&gt;serve as your desktop computer&lt;/a&gt;? History shows such solutions have not worked well because there are too many compromises. In my opinion high performance wireless video is the missing ingredient.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 13 Aug 2018 16:31:37 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/08/13/would-you-buy.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/08/13/would-you-buy.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I didn’t come to micro.blog because I was leaving somewhere else, consequently I don’t see it as an alternative to anything.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 12 Aug 2018 17:17:46 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/08/12/i-didnt-come.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/08/12/i-didnt-come.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Stop!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://frankmcpherson.blog/uploads/2018/27ec8b9e45.jpg&quot; width=&quot;600&quot; height=&quot;600&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Aug 2018 16:04:50 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/08/10/stop.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/08/10/stop.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Happy anniversary&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://frankmcpherson.blog/uploads/2018/404bedfba9.jpg&quot; width=&quot;600&quot; height=&quot;600&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Aug 2018 12:28:18 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/08/10/happy-anniversary.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/08/10/happy-anniversary.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://frankmcpherson.blog/uploads/2018/66e2ed8bc0.jpg&quot; width=&quot;600&quot; height=&quot;600&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Aug 2018 11:51:50 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/08/10/155150.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/08/10/155150.html</guid>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
