<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Frank McPherson</title>
    <description>Follow &lt;a href=&quot;https://micro.blog/frankm&quot;&gt;@frankm on Micro.blog&lt;/a&gt;.</description>
    <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/</link>
    <pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2018 17:10:56 -0500</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2018 17:10:56 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
      <item>
      	
        <title>Carnival In Da Moonlight</title>
        
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mtu.edu/carnival/&quot;&gt;Michigan Tech’s annual Winter Carnival&lt;/a&gt; is in progress, with the snow statue competition completing this morning. I attended Tech from 1984-89 and have good Carny memories. The number of hours students put in to building these statues is incredible and the results are fantastic. Check out &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.flickr.com/photos/michigantech/collections/72157662834921158/&quot;&gt;the photos&lt;/a&gt;! &lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2018 17:10:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/02/08/carnival-in-da.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/02/08/carnival-in-da.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Is it just me, or does it seem the refresh/load times for Timeline and Discover are getting slower? Noticing on web and iOS. &lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2018 11:07:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/02/08/is-it-just.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/02/08/is-it-just.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Love Facebook. Someone thinks it’s ok to enable one to create a group that all their friends automatically join. &lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2018 11:02:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/02/08/love-facebook-someone.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/02/08/love-facebook-someone.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;What’s really behind &lt;a href=&quot;http://scripting.com/2018/02/08.html&quot;&gt;the massive, forceful, push to HTTPS&lt;/a&gt;? It doesn’t make sense to me that it must be used for every site. To achieve their apparent ends, HTTPS needs to be as easy and as expensive to implement as HTTP. &lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 08 Feb 2018 10:28:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/02/08/whats-really-behind.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/02/08/whats-really-behind.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Does anyone know of a smart light bulb or plug that does not automatically turn on after a power failure? It’s frustrating me that I cannot find one that allows me to configure what I want the default state to be. Plugs seem to default to last known state while light bulbs seem to default to on. &lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2018 18:02:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/02/05/does-anyone-know.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/02/05/does-anyone-know.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I watched most of &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.netflix.com/title/80097140&quot;&gt;Altered Carbon&lt;/a&gt; over the weekend and enjoyed it very much. Recommended.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2018 09:10:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/02/05/i-watched-most.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/02/05/i-watched-most.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I think one of the best things about micro.blog is that there are real people behind the posts, just sharing whatever may be of interest, rather than entities using it to gain my attention. &lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2018 09:04:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/02/05/i-think-one.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/02/05/i-think-one.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://the-narthex.org/2018/02/03/doubt-and-hope/&quot;&gt;the-narthex.org&lt;/a&gt; Doubt and Hope &lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 03 Feb 2018 20:30:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/02/03/013056.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/02/04/013056.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cnet.com/news/microsoft-surface-laptop-sale/&quot;&gt;Cnet thinks&lt;/a&gt; $799 for a Windows S notebook that has Core M, 4 GB RAM, 128 GB SSD is a good deal. Wrong! That’s a good deal at $600 and no more. &lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2018 17:21:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/02/02/222141.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/02/02/222141.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;It does look as though &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.theverge.com/2018/2/2/16965520/google-chrome-os-64-update-android-tablets-operating-system-replace&quot;&gt;ChromeOS will be used for tablets&lt;/a&gt; given that Google doesn’t have an official Android tablet at the moment. I still think it needs to be pushed more as a competitor to the Microsoft Surface rather than the iPad. &lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2018 17:18:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/02/02/it-does-look.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/02/02/it-does-look.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I got my Peel, &lt;a href=&quot;https://buypeel.com/products/super-thin-pixel-2-case&quot;&gt;Super Thin Pixel 2 case&lt;/a&gt;, and it is indeed very small and very light. So small and light that I now realize frequent removal may be problematic without breaking the case. OTOH, it enables one to retain the Pixel 2’s small size where the other Google cases I have been using do add bulk.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2018 13:40:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/02/02/i-got-my.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/02/02/i-got-my.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.eltonjohn.com/tours&quot;&gt;We have a date&lt;/a&gt; on the Yellow Brick Road on October 12. &lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2018 10:20:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/02/02/we-have-a.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/02/02/we-have-a.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;The other day I was looking for an iOS app that could access and download files form an Amazon S3 bucket. The only real one I could find was Transmit, which cost $10 and is being removed from the store. I search more, but finding no others, I paid the $10 and bought it even though it likely will not be maintained. It did the job and probably will do so for a while until Amazon changes their API. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Unfortunately, I did not see &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.macstories.net/ipad-diaries/ipad-diaries-transmit-replacements-and-ftp-clients/&quot;&gt;this article on Macstories about alternatives to Transmit&lt;/a&gt; and in particular iFiles, which is cheaper and may do the job just as well. &lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2018 14:27:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/02/01/the-other-day.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/02/01/the-other-day.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://shift.newco.co/wtf-is-wrong-with-capitalism-585249daa9c8&quot;&gt;WTF Is Wrong With Capitalism?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;“The true effect of “trickle-down economics,” he writes, “is the way that the ideal of maximizing profit, not shared prosperity, has metastasized from financial markets and so shapes our entire society….”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2018 13:52:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/02/01/wtf-is-wrong.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/02/01/wtf-is-wrong.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Now, all of a sudden, people are waking up to the idea that a &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.slashgear.com/universal-stylus-initiative-its-about-time-for-a-pen-comeback-01517697/&quot;&gt;stylus is not a bad thing&lt;/a&gt; when it comes to tablets. Again, there is a difference between a stylus being an accessory that enables more features and one that is required to operate a device. &lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2018 09:30:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/02/01/now-all-of.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/02/01/now-all-of.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I think all app developers ought to be thinking of cross-platform data access. If I can’t get to my data from the web and any device I may use, I am likely not going to use your app. Hence apps like DevonThink are a show stopper for for me. &lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2018 14:30:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/01/30/i-think-all.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/01/30/i-think-all.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <title>Feedback On The OmniFocus Roadmap</title>
        
        <description>&lt;p&gt;A couple of thoughts about OmniFocus after reading &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.omnigroup.com/blog/omni-roadmap-2018&quot;&gt;Omni’s roadmap for 2018&lt;/a&gt;. 
As an iOS user but not a Mac OS user, I have long heard about OmniFocus and how great it is but never tried it out. A few weeks ago I discovered I could install the iOS version and try it out for free for two weeks, which I did and frankly, it didn’t seem much better than Todoist or 2Do. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My main requirement is multi-platform support because while use an iPad as my primary personal computer, I  also use Android smartphones and Windows notebook computers. The inability to get to info in OmniFocus from Windows has been a show stopper, and web access, which is on the roadmap, will help, however I am concerned about the “minimalist” plan. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A simple way that Omni could solve this problem is by syncing with Toodledo. While there is a Toodledo iOS app, it is not very efficient so I use 2Do on my iPad that syncs my data with Toodledo. The benefit is that there are Toodledo apps for other platforms, and the Toodledo web app is one of the most advanced web apps that I use.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am also surprised that OmniFocus doesn’t use an outliner for editing projects and tasks, given the existence of OmniOutliner, which I do use. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ll keep a watch out for the next release of OmniFocus and probably check it out. &lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2018 13:57:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/01/30/feedback-on-the.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/01/30/feedback-on-the.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://builttoadapt.io/7-recent-books-that-everyone-in-tech-should-read-626acf0d759e&quot;&gt;7 Recent Books That Everyone in Tech Should Read&lt;/a&gt; A book should be written on the topic, just because we &lt;strong&gt;can&lt;/strong&gt; do something doesn’t mean we &lt;strong&gt;should&lt;/strong&gt; do something. &lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2018 09:46:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/01/29/recent-books-that.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/01/29/recent-books-that.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://realpersonalcomputing.com/2018/01/28/use-google-assistant-as-offline-brain/&quot;&gt;realpersonalcomputing.com&lt;/a&gt; Use Google Assistant As Offline Brain. &lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jan 2018 16:57:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/01/28/215702.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/01/28/215702.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Auto correction in iOS frustrates me more than auto correction in Android. &lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jan 2018 13:46:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/01/28/auto-correction-in.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/01/28/auto-correction-in.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://a.co/i7n1jWp&quot;&gt;a.co&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;“The stirring of leaves in the wind makes the wind visible. Their stirring is the wind’s stirring, their whisper is the wind’s whisper. And so with love. Our actions of love make the invisible visible. Our actions of love make love present to ourselves and to others. And as we go out of ourselves in love, and become, as it were, lost in those we love, we discover a self-greater than our isolated ego. We discover the birth of that self born of the death to self-centeredness.” from “Merton’s Palace of Nowhere” by James Finley, Henri J. M. Nouwen&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jan 2018 12:05:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/01/28/acohttpacoinjwp-the-stirring.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/01/28/acohttpacoinjwp-the-stirring.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ew.com/tv/2018/01/17/shannara-chronicles-canceled/&quot;&gt;Spike cancels season 3 of the Shannara Chronicles&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I binged season 2 on Netflix last night, after being surprised to find it as I didn’t know it was made. I read the Shannara books a long time ago and I have fun trying to remember parts of the book while watching, although I know the TV Series is not an exact depiction. &lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2018 14:59:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/01/27/spike-cancels-season.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/01/27/spike-cancels-season.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://flip.it/OvOE.V&quot;&gt;flip.it&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Chome OS is coming to tablets, leaked Acer device suggests http://flip.it/OvOE.V&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Chrome OS 2-in-1s make sense, a tablet does not. &lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2018 14:41:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/01/27/flipithttpflipitovoev-chome-os.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/01/27/flipithttpflipitovoev-chome-os.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://infinitediaries.net/one-hour-with-apples-new-homepod/&quot;&gt;infinitediaries.net&lt;/a&gt; One hour with the Homepod. Yuck. &lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2018 22:17:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/01/25/031722.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/01/26/031722.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I guess some people are using micro.blog to post items to Wordpress. My micro.blogs are &lt;a href=&quot;https://fjmnotes.com&quot;&gt;going to Wordpress&lt;/a&gt; via Twitter, which I am guessing some may consider oxymoronic. &lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2018 22:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/01/25/i-guess-some.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/01/26/i-guess-some.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <title>Capitalism &lt;&gt; Democracy</title>
        
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://eand.co/the-american-dream-is-over-this-is-the-age-of-the-european-dream-71c668bef945&quot;&gt;The American Dream is Over. This is the Age of the European Dream.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One might not agree with the entire premise of the above article, but I think there is something to the point being made that we wrongly think markets/capitalism is the solution to every problem in our country. In fact, one can make the argument that capitalism is the root of much that is wrong in our country. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For example, the reality is capitalism (read revenue and profits) is the true reason why the NRA agressively opposes any gun control; the NRA’s corporate supporters make a lot of money off the sale of guns and ammunition and logically do not want any of that money to be at risk. Just like capitalism drove the tobacco industry to ignore studies showing smoking causes cancer. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For a long time I have been saying that we tend to confuse capitalism with democracy. I think this is reflected most prominently by the &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.scotusblog.com/case-files/cases/citizens-united-v-federal-election-commission/&quot;&gt;Citizens United&lt;/a&gt; SCOTUS ruling that says corporate spending on politics is a form of free speech, and thus corporations have a right to free speech.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Corporations are a construct of capitalism, they are not in themselves men or women of any race. In otherwords, corporations are not citizens. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Citizens United may be the worst SCOTUS ruling of my lifetime. Worse, it is reflects a flawed understanding that frankly skews society in favor of corporations and the oligarchs that profit from them. &lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2018 11:50:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/01/25/capitalism-democracy.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/01/25/capitalism-democracy.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I think Michigan State University President &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.chicagotribune.com/sports/college/ct-michigan-state-lou-anna-simon-larry-nassar-20180124-story.html&quot;&gt;Lou Anna Simon’s resignation letter&lt;/a&gt; says a lot for why Larry Nassar was enabled by the university. The following statement says to me, “I am not to blame, but since I am the President I am the scapegoat.” MSU Alumni, parents, and students ought to be appalled by what appears to be institutionalized problems.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;As tragedies are politicized, blame is inevitable. As president, it is only natural that I am the focus of this anger.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2018 08:33:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/01/25/i-think-michigan.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/01/25/i-think-michigan.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://chrome.google.com/webstore/detail/web-server-for-chrome/ofhbbkphhbklhfoeikjpcbhemlocgigb&quot;&gt;Web server for Chrome&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2018 15:19:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/01/23/web-server-for.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/01/23/web-server-for.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;“During this year iOS users will be spending about $100 million per day for Apps. This was Google’s AdWords revenue rate in 2012.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.asymco.com/2018/01/08/the-ios-economy-updated/&quot;&gt;The iOS Economy, Updated&lt;/a&gt; via Instapaper&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2018 21:43:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/01/22/during-this-year.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/01/23/during-this-year.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Is there an advantage to &lt;a href=&quot;https://agiletortoise.com/drafts/screencasts/&quot;&gt;writing something in Draft&lt;/a&gt;s and then pushing it over to micro.blog? One reason is that it is faster to paste a hyperlink into a post in Drafts than in the micro.blog iOS app. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Drafts and Workflow are the two iOS apps that I really want to learn more about this year. &lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2018 20:32:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/01/22/is-there-an.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/01/23/is-there-an.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Despite articles to the contrary, Android Wear keeps ticking along. The latest evidence is &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.digitaltrends.com/wearables/tag-heuer-connected-modular-41-smartwatch-news/&quot;&gt;Tag Heuer’s newest watch&lt;/a&gt;. I believe more so than smartphones, Android Wear is really in the background such that it is more about companies like Tag Heuer and Fossil versus the Apple iWatch. &lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2018 14:21:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/01/22/despite-articles-to.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/01/22/despite-articles-to.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;One can buy a 128 GB 9.7-inch iPad &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.macrumors.com/2018/01/22/target-apple-watch-series-1-staples/&quot;&gt;at Staples for $359&lt;/a&gt;. The barrier of entry to tablets is getting lower every day. &lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2018 13:31:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/01/22/one-can-buy.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/01/22/one-can-buy.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://a.co/exVBzoj&quot;&gt;a.co&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;“Who I am must never be prostituted to the demands of what others tell me I must do. Without this basic priority I am reduced to a commodity and I can do little to foster society’s half-hidden yet essential purpose of leading its members to full actualization as created persons.” from “Merton’s Palace of Nowhere” by James Finley, Henri J. M. Nouwen&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2018 11:56:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/01/21/acohttpacoexvbzoj-who-i.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/01/21/acohttpacoexvbzoj-who-i.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;It’s &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bellsbeer.com/news/shipping-dates-state-hopslam-2018-other-helpful-links&quot;&gt;Hopslam time&lt;/a&gt;. I had my first can this evening. &lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2018 00:34:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/01/21/053441.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/01/21/053441.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_Gf4jN1xoSo&amp;amp;feature=share&quot;&gt;The true origins of the religious right &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jan 2018 11:38:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/01/20/the-true-origins.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/01/20/the-true-origins.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;If you want to decrease or stop abortions you have to first correctly identify what causes abortions, and that is not a Supreme Court ruling. &lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jan 2018 10:37:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/01/20/if-you-want.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/01/20/if-you-want.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Why would a web site load in mobile web browsers but not on a desktop? &lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jan 2018 10:36:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/01/18/why-would-a.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/01/18/why-would-a.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <title>Hanselminutes: Raspberry Pi clusters and Serverless</title>
        
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://blog.alexellis.io/serverless-hanselminutes/&quot;&gt;blog.alexellis.io/serverles…&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This entry is coming from Feedbin, does this get posted to my blog or just added to the Timeline? &lt;strong&gt;Update:&lt;/strong&gt; So, this did end up on the blog, interesting. I wonder if the same thing happens with Evergreen? &lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jan 2018 09:44:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/01/18/hanselminutes-raspberry-pi.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/01/18/hanselminutes-raspberry-pi.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Based on the number of references in my timeline, I am checking out Feedbin. I am not sure that an integrated solution such as this fits my workflow, but I do find that it’s article count for each feed is giving me an opportunity to prune my RSS subscriptions. &lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jan 2018 09:32:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/01/18/based-on-the.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/01/18/based-on-the.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <title>Yet Again Focusing On The Wrong Thing</title>
        
        <description>&lt;p&gt;The lesson to be learned from the false missile alert in Hawaii is &lt;strong&gt;not&lt;/strong&gt; how someone screwed up, a bad communication plan, nor &lt;a href=&quot;https://hackernoon.com/redesigning-hawaiis-emergy-alert-interface-in-the-open-91c6318a7045?b9&quot;&gt;bad UI design&lt;/a&gt;. The lesson that &lt;strong&gt;should be&lt;/strong&gt; learned is that the possibility of a nuclear strick on the United States is much more plausible today that it has since the cold war. We appear to be nearing &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.history.com/topics/cold-war/cuban-missile-crisis&quot;&gt;Cuban Missile Crisis&lt;/a&gt; territory with incompetent leadership in the government. &lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2018 10:53:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/01/17/yet-again-focusing.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/01/17/yet-again-focusing.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;The first college basketball game (unofficial) was played &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.loc.gov/item/today-in-history/january-16?loclr=eatod#chicago-dunks-iowa&quot;&gt;on this day in 1896.&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2018 09:25:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/01/16/the-first-college.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/01/16/the-first-college.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;In most cases athletes need to just react to the circumstances in front of them in order to perform. What often separates professionals is the extent to which they repetitively practice so what they need to do is more instinct and that allows their atheticism to shine. If an athlete thinks too much during a play, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cbssports.com/nfl/news/marcus-williams-who-whiffed-on-stefon-diggs-walk-off-td-explains-what-happened&quot;&gt;you sometimes end up doing what the New Orleans Saints safety did&lt;/a&gt; in the final play of the game on Sunday.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2018 09:10:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/01/16/in-most-causes.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/01/16/in-most-causes.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Last month was one of my &lt;a href=&quot;http://writing.frankmcpherson.org/2017/12/&quot;&gt;better blogging months.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2018 21:44:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/01/15/last-month-was.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/01/16/last-month-was.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.patrickrhone.net/faces-like-these/&quot;&gt;Faces Like These – Rhoneisms&lt;/a&gt; Just putting this here as a reminder. Hope. &lt;a href=&quot;https://micro.blog/patrickrhone&quot;&gt;@patrickrhone&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2018 21:11:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/01/15/faces-like-these.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/01/16/faces-like-these.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://medium.com/@caspervonb/a-brief-totally-accurate-history-of-programming-languages-cd93ec806124&quot;&gt;A Brief Totally Accurate History of Programming Languages&lt;/a&gt; is a good read. &lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2018 18:01:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/01/15/a-brief-totally.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/01/15/a-brief-totally.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I wish that read later web apps like Pocket and Instapaper supported sharing to blogs &lt;a href=&quot;http://inessential.com/2018/01/15/evergreen_diary_4_send_to_micro_blog&quot;&gt;as described by Brent&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2018 13:55:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/01/15/i-wish-that.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/01/15/i-wish-that.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;As great as the 🏈 games were today, we saw many terrible coaching decisions that arguably cost their team the game. &lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 14 Jan 2018 20:41:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/01/14/as-great-as.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/01/15/as-great-as.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;At least there is some drama in the Saints/Vikings game. #football &lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 14 Jan 2018 19:37:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/01/14/at-least-there.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/01/15/at-least-there.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;The power button on my wife’s Moto G4 broke and I have found that there is no way to restart a phone with no power button. Shouldn’t there be such an option within settings? (Btw, we are replacing the G4 with a G5s plus.)&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2018 15:35:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/01/13/the-power-button.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/01/13/the-power-button.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;One of my favorite features of micro.blog is that you and tap an entry in the timeline and select Conversation to read an entire thread. &lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2018 15:32:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/01/13/one-of-my.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/01/13/one-of-my.html</guid>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
