<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Frank McPherson's Web Notes</title>
    <description>Follow &lt;a href=&quot;https://micro.blog/frankm&quot;&gt;@frankm on Micro.blog&lt;/a&gt;.</description>
    <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/</link>
    <pubDate>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 09:41:51 -0400</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 09:41:51 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I am wearing a Fossil Q Explorist, third generation. Battery life has been good enough to get through my day up until recently. It’s hard to get solid evidence because the Wear OS app does not provide much useful info on power drainers. It feels as though the problem started when upgrading my Pixel 2 to Android P. Doing a factory resert and re-pair to see if that fixes it.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 09:41:22 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/09/14/i-am-wearing.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/09/14/i-am-wearing.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.atlasobscura.com/articles/colorado-brewery-water-shortage.amp&quot;&gt;Water shortages affecting beer production&lt;/a&gt;. Oh the horror!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 13 Sep 2018 17:31:49 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/09/13/water-shortages-affecting.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/09/13/water-shortages-affecting.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/ios/comments/9fel8k/i_thought_siri_shortcuts_was_a_suppose_to_be_an/&quot;&gt;Where is the Siri Shortcuts app&lt;/a&gt;? I have the official iOS 12 release on my iPads and the app is not included.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 13 Sep 2018 17:23:26 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/09/13/where-is-the.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/09/13/where-is-the.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Can one &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.zdnet.com/article/apple-finally-moves-beyond-the-shadow-of-steve-jobs-with-a-truly-life-changing-product/?ftag=TREc64629f&amp;amp;bhid=22245710784390860490896261461221&quot;&gt;use an Apple Watch&lt;/a&gt; without an iPhone? If not, the barrier to entry for someone who does not own an IPhone is awfully high.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 13 Sep 2018 17:05:24 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/09/13/can-one-use.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/09/13/can-one-use.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;While you can configure the Gmail app to use the same categories as Inbox, Gmail does not have a simple way to archive all messages in a category. For example, I want to see all Updates, scan through the list, and quickly archive them after I’ve read what I want to read. Gmail also does not have a button to snooze a message, but at least you can configure one of the two swipe actions to snooze.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ack! Just realize that when I implemented categories (Primary, Social, Promotions, Updates, and Forums) in the Gmail app on my phone, that changes the web version of Gmail too. Worse, there is no single button way to archive all email of a category. You first have to select all messages and then buttons appear to mark read, archive, delete, etc..&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, Google, give me an easy way to archive all email in a category in Gmail and I will be unaffected by the demise of Inbox. Think about how fast it is to triage email in Inbox and enable that same capability in Gmail.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 13 Sep 2018 09:08:28 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/09/13/while-you-can.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/09/13/while-you-can.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Really disappointed by the news that &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.theverge.com/2018/9/12/17848500/google-inbox-shut-down-sunset-snooze-email-march-2019&quot;&gt;Google will be shutting down Inbox&lt;/a&gt;. I think it is the best email app for smartphones because it makes it real easy to triage email.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am not surprised by the news, we saw this coming and I’ve been using the Gmail app on desktop and tablets and Inbox on my Pixel and iPad Mini.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 13 Sep 2018 09:02:13 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/09/13/really-disappointed-by.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/09/13/really-disappointed-by.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;There is an event going on this afternoon at which &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.theverge.com/2018/9/12/17849898/apple-confirms-iphone-xs-iphone-xs-max-iphone-xr-names&quot;&gt;rumor has it&lt;/a&gt; we might see what is called an iPhone XS or iPhone super-sized.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 12 Sep 2018 08:55:12 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/09/12/there-is-an.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/09/12/there-is-an.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <title>The Right To Not Be Forgotten</title>
        
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://scripting.com&quot;&gt;Dave Winer&lt;/a&gt; has been writing about owning and archiving what one writes and publishes on the web for a very long time. I think the heart of the matter is that if one is to think of the web as a library there has to be a mechanism for it to be long-lived.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In other words, permanence. The interesting thing is that many people dislike the web’s permanence, and the &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Right_to_be_forgotten&quot;&gt;European Union even has a law&lt;/a&gt; in place intended to enable people to disrupt that permanence.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you do see the value, however, there needs to be permanent access to what is written and a way to get to it. Permanently storing files is a whole lot easier than permanent access.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://scripting.com/2018/09/10/161928.html&quot;&gt;Dave currently thinks&lt;/a&gt; Github may be as good as anything given that it is owned by Microsoft, a company one expects will be around for a while Still, given that it is a corporate asset, Github exists at the pleasure of Microsoft and not the public.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To Dave’s point, one thing I like about micro.blog is its support for Github. Micro.blog writes a copy of both the source markdown and the rendered HTML of what I write here to Github, and that provides one degree of backup. However, it gets even better because I use git to maintain a clone of that repository on my local computers, which provides me an easy backup copy of what I write on a computer I own.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The markdown is source for jekyll, which itself is an open source blog platform, and that source boils down to plain text files. BTW, jekyll itself works in this manner with Github pages which is good enough for many people, but I happen to like social layer and community that micro.blog provides.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 10 Sep 2018 16:51:56 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/09/10/dave-winer-has.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/09/10/dave-winer-has.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.omegacenter.info/death-in-church-new-life-ahead/&quot;&gt;Barbara Brown Taylor&lt;/a&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Human beings were so charmed by the illusion of control Newton’s metaphor offered that we began to see ourselves as machines too. Believing that Newton told us the truth about how the world works, we modeled our institutions on atomistic principles.
…
Our “God view” came to resemble our worldview. In this century, even much of our practical theology has also become mechanical and atomistic. Walk into many churches and you will hear God described as a being who behaves almost as predictably as Newton’s universe. Say you believe in God and you will be saved.  Sin against God and you will be condemned. Say you are sorry and you will be forgiven.  Obey the law and you will be blessed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 10 Sep 2018 15:55:46 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/09/10/barbara-brown-taylor.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/09/10/barbara-brown-taylor.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.omegacenter.info/schism-or-evolution/&quot;&gt;Ilia Delio, OSF&lt;/a&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;The Benedict Church holds that orthodoxy or the true teaching of the Church resides in the unbroken apostolic tradition of the Petrine tradition, the men ordained and ontologically changed by the sacrament of Holy Orders.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In my opinion, the above is the closest I’ve seen written to what I think is the root problem within the Roman Catholic church. It is too simplistic to state the problem is gay priests or celibacy or not ordaining women, all those are simply symptoms to the problem, a problem more closely related to why the Roman Catholic church exists as an institution.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 10 Sep 2018 15:14:09 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/09/10/ilia-delio-osf.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/09/10/ilia-delio-osf.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Whenever I see &lt;a href=&quot;https://9to5mac.com/2018/09/10/kuo-iphone-6-1-ipad-pro-usb-c-macbook-touch-id-apple-watch-ecg/&quot;&gt;an article&lt;/a&gt; about an Apple product that has the words “low price” I ask, define low price.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 10 Sep 2018 13:24:48 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/09/10/whenever-i-see.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/09/10/whenever-i-see.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;The Packers made &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.espn.com/nfl/story/_/id/24629977/aaron-rodgers-knee-green-back-packers-returns-game&quot;&gt;an incredible comeback&lt;/a&gt; last night because of Aaron Rodgers. The fact that team is so dependent on one player is nearly negligent. Wouldn’t it be prudent to have an experienced backup?&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 10 Sep 2018 13:22:04 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/09/10/the-packers-made.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/09/10/the-packers-made.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://techpinions.com/the-post-pc-era-never-really-happened-and-likely-wont/53610&quot;&gt;The ‘Post-PC Era’ Never Really Happened…and Likely Won’t&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Of course not, &lt;a href=&quot;https://realpersonalcomputing.com/2011/12/26/post-pc-era-or-the-beginning-of-the-personal-computing-era/&quot;&gt;I wrote about this nearly seven years ago&lt;/a&gt;. Post-PC has always really been the transformation to the &lt;strong&gt;real&lt;/strong&gt; personal computing and not how personal computing had been previously defined.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 10 Sep 2018 13:15:21 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/09/10/the-postpc-era.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/09/10/the-postpc-era.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I’ve been waiting all day for Sunday night. Go Pack go!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 09 Sep 2018 20:02:07 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/09/09/ive-been-waiting.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/09/10/ive-been-waiting.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Do the announcers of NFL games not know how idiotic the phrase “cannot tackle with all of your body weight” is? How does a defender tackle someone with half or part of their body weight?&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 09 Sep 2018 15:18:58 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/09/09/do-the-announcers.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/09/09/do-the-announcers.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;So, you can’t tackle a NFL quarterback anymore?&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 09 Sep 2018 14:49:53 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/09/09/so-you-cant.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/09/09/so-you-cant.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Forgotten in how the women’s final of the U.S. Open ended is that the problems started with one of the most asinine rules of professional sports. Just stop having tennis chair umpires policing “coaching” from the stands. No gesture made by a coach is going to make a difference, the players still have to execute. Further, the rule is not in any way consistently applied.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tennis is not “special” because players are on their own, and fans pay good money to watch the players decide that match, not umpires.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 08 Sep 2018 20:31:49 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/09/08/forgotten-in-how.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/09/09/forgotten-in-how.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Osaka is playing with seemingly no pressure. At twenty years old you figure you will be in many more slams, so no pressure if you lose.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 08 Sep 2018 16:58:24 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/09/08/osaka-is-playing.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/09/08/osaka-is-playing.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;The U.S. Open Women’s final feels a bit right now like when Sharapova beat Williams at Wimbledon.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 08 Sep 2018 16:37:21 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/09/08/the-us-open.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/09/08/the-us-open.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://politicalwire.com/2018/09/07/we-are-a-superpower-run-by-a-simpleton/&quot;&gt;Incompetency&lt;/a&gt; is the primary reason why I could not and did not vote for Trump.  Current politics makes the problem worse. Not enough people took competency seriously enough and we are starting to pay the price.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The problem is that too many people confuse politics with competency, by which I mean they don’t think Trump is incompetent they just think Democrats and Republicans are simply preventing him from doing the job.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Sep 2018 11:50:39 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/09/07/incompetency-is-the.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/09/07/incompetency-is-the.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.vox.com/policy-and-politics/2018/9/6/17825406/trump-woodward-op-ed-nyt-anonymous-impeachment&quot;&gt;The anonymous New York Times Trump op-ed tells us what we already knew: Trump is unfit&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;The Founding Fathers were not unaware of the possibility that a demagogue or a knave might win the presidency. That’s why they checked the executive with an independent Congress and built in powers of impeachment. That Republicans in this Congress have proven so subservient to — or scared of — Trump that they have let the fate of the country hinge on whether his staff can adequately distract and calm him is a subversion of the constitutional order and an abdication of responsibility.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 06 Sep 2018 18:05:26 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/09/06/the-anonymous-new.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/09/06/the-anonymous-new.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Maybe it is just me, but I think Google Chrome’s new UI is a little cartoonish.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 06 Sep 2018 17:55:50 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/09/06/maybe-it-is.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/09/06/maybe-it-is.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://frankmcpherson.blog/uploads/2018/dd90ad916c.jpg&quot; width=&quot;600&quot; height=&quot;600&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 06 Sep 2018 08:54:19 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/09/06/125419.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/09/06/125419.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Happy &lt;a href=&quot;https://906day.com/&quot;&gt;906 Day&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you are near Lake Superior, today is a good day to take ride, pick up a pasty, and enjoy the beauty of the lake.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://frankmcpherson.blog/uploads/2018/81827420da.jpg&quot; width=&quot;600&quot; height=&quot;450&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Take a few moments to &lt;a href=&quot;https://upsupply.co/upper-peninsula&quot;&gt;learn about the Upper Peninsula of Michigan&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 06 Sep 2018 08:42:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/09/06/happy-day-if.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/09/06/happy-day-if.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.chicagotribune.com/news/ct-met-ohare-oasis-shutdown-20180905-story.html#nws=true&quot;&gt;The O’Hare Oasis is now closed&lt;/a&gt;. Making way for progress.  In my travels around Chicago, I usually stop at the Hinsdale and Lake Forest Oasises(?) so this won’t personally affect me, but sad just the same.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 05 Sep 2018 13:35:47 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/09/05/the-ohare-oasis.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/09/05/the-ohare-oasis.html</guid>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
