<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Frank McPherson's Web Notes</title>
    <description>Follow &lt;a href=&quot;https://micro.blog/frankm&quot;&gt;@frankm on Micro.blog&lt;/a&gt;.</description>
    <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/</link>
    <pubDate>Sun, 12 Aug 2018 17:18:01 -0400</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 12 Aug 2018 17:18:01 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I didn’t come to micro.blog because I was leaving somewhere else, consequently I don’t see it as an alternative to anything.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 12 Aug 2018 17:17:46 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/08/12/i-didnt-come.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/08/12/i-didnt-come.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Stop!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://frankmcpherson.blog/uploads/2018/27ec8b9e45.jpg&quot; width=&quot;600&quot; height=&quot;600&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Aug 2018 16:04:50 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/08/10/stop.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/08/10/stop.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Happy anniversary&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://frankmcpherson.blog/uploads/2018/404bedfba9.jpg&quot; width=&quot;600&quot; height=&quot;600&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Aug 2018 12:28:18 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/08/10/happy-anniversary.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/08/10/happy-anniversary.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://frankmcpherson.blog/uploads/2018/66e2ed8bc0.jpg&quot; width=&quot;600&quot; height=&quot;600&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Aug 2018 11:51:50 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/08/10/155150.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/08/10/155150.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;O-Hi&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://frankmcpherson.blog/uploads/2018/a7bf512bea.jpg&quot; width=&quot;600&quot; height=&quot;600&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 09 Aug 2018 15:31:09 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/08/09/ohi.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/08/09/ohi.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Road trip #happyanniversary&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://frankmcpherson.blog/uploads/2018/da85437b6d.jpg&quot; width=&quot;600&quot; height=&quot;600&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 09 Aug 2018 13:57:38 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/08/09/road-trip-happyanniversary.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/08/09/road-trip-happyanniversary.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://inessential.com/2018/08/08/the_public_square&quot;&gt;inessential: The Public Square&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I fear calling the web a public square, thinking that is is truly open, is a myth. All of the infrastructure upon which the web runs is owned by corporations. The technology upon which the web is built is intended to be open, but they are under control of corporations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Corporations pushed the web towards HTML5 in support of apps that they utlimately control. Corporations own the browsers that we use and with coding changes can force all of use towards a direction they want. The network infrastructure upon which the packets ride are owned by corporations who can, and have, allowed governments to capture and review those packets.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sure, you can host content on a web server running in your house. What happens when Comcast or AT&amp;amp;T decides to not sell Internet access to you? What happens when the coporations that control DNS remove your domain from their servers, or direct requests somewhere else?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;None of this is truly open. All of it is at risk if it does not serve coporate interests. Right now the best we have are degrees of openness.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 09 Aug 2018 11:22:33 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/08/09/inessential-the-public.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/08/09/inessential-the-public.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Most of &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.theverge.com/2018/8/8/17663494/microsoft-surface-go-review-specs-performance&quot;&gt;the reviews&lt;/a&gt; that I have read about the Surface Go have been positive. First, I note that all reviews are of the high-end, 8 GB model. Second, I can’t help but feel that everyone is desperate for a competitor to the iPad and therefore will praise up any attempt.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Personally, I think the main issue is price. At a minimum Microsoft should be bundling the keyboard with the device at the price of that $650 price. I would love to see info on how many Surfaces are sold without keyboard.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now, it may look as though I am really down on the Surface Go, while I think I am neutral. I do think that if you are looking at a device for viewing video, you might want to give the Go a ago because of the built-in stand. If you just consume content you can live without the keyboard and stylus.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 08 Aug 2018 16:30:20 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/08/08/most-of-the.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/08/08/most-of-the.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I started using Instapaper because Pocket charges to highlight text. Now that &lt;a href=&quot;http://blog.instapaper.com/post/176732408411&quot;&gt;Instapaper plans to charge $30 a year for notes&lt;/a&gt;, I need to decide whether I want to stay or switch back to Pocket.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 07 Aug 2018 17:52:40 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/08/07/i-started-using.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/08/07/i-started-using.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;There are some &lt;a href=&quot;https://palash.tk/Start-Photography-With-Android&quot;&gt;good suggestions here&lt;/a&gt; of alternatives to the Camera app that you find on your Android phone. I confess that I don’t think much about the pictures that I take, I just use the build-in camera and upload to Google.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 07 Aug 2018 13:25:50 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/08/07/there-are-some.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/08/07/there-are-some.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Do we still know what parts of the Internet are the public’s and which part is the corporations? &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.history.com/news/who-invented-the-internet&quot;&gt;The Internet began as a U.S. Department of Defense project&lt;/a&gt;, funded by taxpayers and therefore owned by the public. At a minimum that part of the Internet should be open with free speech protections, but can we even find it?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our unwillingness to create new utilities, owned and protected by the government (too much like socialism) is to our detriment. Government should do more than spend billions on defense and enable corporate owners to get rich.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 07 Aug 2018 09:08:33 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/08/07/do-we-still.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/08/07/do-we-still.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I have built myself a remote Linux Ubuntu/XFCE session using &lt;a href=&quot;https://cepa.io/2018/08/05/building-an-ultimate-remote-linux-workstation/&quot;&gt;these instructions&lt;/a&gt; and a VM I created at &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cloudatcost.com&quot;&gt;CloudAtClost&lt;/a&gt;. The VM I created had 2 vCPUs and 2 GB of RAM and runs pretty well, at least for text entry and email processing. Now, if only I could find a working X2GO client for iOS, the one in the app store does not run on my iPad Pro.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 06 Aug 2018 20:02:42 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/08/06/i-have-built.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/08/07/i-have-built.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.google/products/android/introducing-android-9-pie/&quot;&gt;Google has formally released Android 9&lt;/a&gt;, which will informally be known as Android Pie (P is for Pie). The nanny, otherwise known as &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.android.com/versions/pie-9-0/&quot;&gt;Digital Wellbeing&lt;/a&gt;, will launch in the fall. I am not surprised by the release as the beta I have been running has been very stable.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 06 Aug 2018 16:38:10 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/08/06/google-has-formally.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/08/06/google-has-formally.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I thought this weekend I had my first fatality due to &lt;a href=&quot;https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/07/26/ive-been-running.html&quot;&gt;upgrading my Pixel 2 to Android P&lt;/a&gt;. The Starbucks app on my phone lost my login information and I couldn’t get it to signin. It took me a day to contemplate the issue before I decided to uninstall and reinstall the app, which fixed the problem.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 06 Aug 2018 10:01:08 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/08/06/i-thought-this.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/08/06/i-thought-this.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://nymag.com/daily/intelligencer/2018/08/frank-rich-2008-financial-crisis-end-of-american-dream.html&quot;&gt;Frank Rich: In 2008, America Stopped Believing in the American Dream&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;In Behold, America, a fascinating new look at “the entangled history” of “America First” and “the American Dream,” out this fall, Sarah Churchwell unearths a 1900 editorial in the New York Post fretting about how multimillionaires “are very rarely, if ever, content with a position of equality.” The paper hypothesized that “the American dream,” a term not yet in common parlance, could be ended by their greed. A similar 1908 editorial in the Leavenworth, Kansas, Times, again invoking “American dreams,” championed “the equitable distribution of wealth” while making pointed note of the vast discrepancy between the pay of an insurance-company executive and a headmaster: “Why do we accord highest place to money mongers and lowest place to teachers of ideals?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 06 Aug 2018 09:46:24 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/08/06/frank-rich-in.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/08/06/frank-rich-in.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://the-narthex.org/2011/03/11/saving-jesus-redux/&quot;&gt;Saving Jesus Redux – Learning From Others, Seeking The Way&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I hope the embedded video provides food for thought.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 05 Aug 2018 14:40:47 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/08/05/saving-jesus-redux.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/08/05/saving-jesus-redux.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://androidcommunity.com/android-p-will-reportedly-be-rolled-out-on-august-20-20180803/&quot;&gt;Android P will reportedly be rolled out on August 20 - Android Community&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ve been running Android P on my Pixel 2 for a couple of weeks and I have not had any problems with it. I also think it is an iterative improvement on Oreo, meaning that if you don’t have It you aren’t necessarily missing out.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.androidpolice.com/2018/07/24/every-new-android-p-feature-weve-found-far-continuously-updated/&quot;&gt;Android Police has a complete rundown&lt;/a&gt; of all the new things. Oddly, my favorite may be the charging sound, as I have had cases when I thought I was charging my phone when I wasn’t because the charger was completely plugged in.  The cleaned up settings and notifications are nice, and the navigation improvements are ok but not amazing. I am still looking for significant improvement in battery life.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 04 Aug 2018 12:50:46 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/08/04/android-p-will.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/08/04/android-p-will.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.axios.com/dnc-warns-candidates-to-not-use-zte-huawei-devices-b9a9246c-1f26-42cb-8989-b2c307011750.html&quot;&gt;Democratic National Committee warns candidates to not use ZTE, Huawei devices - Axios&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Maybe the DNC should be teaching their members about social engineering, phishing, and good security hygiene. Most hacks occur between the brain and the fingers.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 04 Aug 2018 12:08:53 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/08/04/democratic-national-committee.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/08/04/democratic-national-committee.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.computerworld.com/article/3293900/android/snap-between-apps-android.html&quot;&gt;A better way to snap between apps on Android - Computerworld&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am still in the process of building muscle memory around the gestures in Android P, but this looks like a useful addition to Android.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Aug 2018 13:21:10 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/08/03/a-better-way.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/08/03/a-better-way.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I am pretty much following &lt;a href=&quot;https://indieweb.org/POSSE&quot;&gt;POSSE&lt;/a&gt;, hosting my content with domains I own on either &lt;a href=&quot;https://frankmcpherson.blog&quot;&gt;micro.blog&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href=&quot;https://writing.frankmcpherson.net&quot;&gt;Netlify&lt;/a&gt;, and syndicating that content to &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/frankm&quot;&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/writtenbyfrank&quot;&gt;Facebook&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href=&quot;https://fjmnotes.com&quot;&gt;Wordpress&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One problem with this approach is that syndication only occurs once. If I make edits, like I just did (you will notice a typo in the related tweet) the corresponding syndicated item is not changed. I think this highlights one of the main differences between blogs and social networks. Blogs abide the reality that we make mistakes and provides an easy why to correct those mistakes, and social networks do not.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One strange thing syndicating to Wordpress is that just about every post I make there gets liked by someone new. While I know some of the likes are from real people, it feels like bots.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Aug 2018 10:09:17 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/08/03/the-am-pretty.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/08/03/the-am-pretty.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Good morning!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Aug 2018 09:09:52 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/08/03/good-morning.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/08/03/good-morning.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://laughingsquid.com/joe-walsh-explains-lifes-been-good/&quot;&gt;Musician Joe Walsh Hilariously Explains the Meaning of ‘Life’s Been Good’ to a Live Audience&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Great story behind the song.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 02 Aug 2018 23:04:34 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/08/02/musician-joe-walsh.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/08/03/musician-joe-walsh.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.engadget.com/2018/08/02/surface-go-review/&quot;&gt;Surface Go review: The ideal cheap Windows tablet… almost&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I bought the Surface 3 because of its support for an active digitizer. Now that the iPad supports the Apple Pencil and it is cheaper than the Surface Go, it would be really hard for me to pick the Go over the iPad.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ever since I bought the iPad Pro 10.5 my Surface 3 has been relegated to role as my only computer running Windows 10. I picked up a refurbed dock for a low price, and the Surface 3 sits in that dock pretty much unused until I have a need to run Windows on a computer that I own. So far all releases of Windows 10 run on it, so I don’t really have a need to replace or retire it until it can no longer be patched.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 02 Aug 2018 22:44:05 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/08/02/surface-go-review.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/08/03/surface-go-review.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;The founders of the United States did not intend the President to be the most powerful man in the world.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 02 Aug 2018 11:03:48 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/08/02/the-founders-of.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/08/02/the-founders-of.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I’ve been keeping an eye out for the Acer Chromebook Spin 13, but &lt;a href=&quot;https://liliputing.com/2018/08/acer-chromebook-13-chromebook-spin-13-coming-in-september-for-650-and-up.html?utm_source=feedburner&amp;amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;amp;utm_campaign=Feed%3A+Liliputing+%28Liliputing%29&quot;&gt;now that I see the pricing&lt;/a&gt; I am conflicted. At that $750 price it might be worth just buying the current Google Pixelbook.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 02 Aug 2018 10:49:12 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/08/02/ive-been-keeping.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/08/02/ive-been-keeping.html</guid>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
