<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Frank McPherson</title>
    <description>Follow &lt;a href=&quot;https://micro.blog/frankm&quot;&gt;@frankm on Micro.blog&lt;/a&gt;.</description>
    <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/</link>
    <pubDate>Sat, 05 May 2018 15:18:07 -0400</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 05 May 2018 15:18:07 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Watching the Cubs play the Cardinals. So far two calls have been overturned by replay. Replay is showing how bad baseball umpires are, you can almost say something like 25% of all calls made in MLB history before replay were wrong.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 05 May 2018 15:18:06 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/05/05/watching-the-cubs.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/05/05/watching-the-cubs.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Does anyone have a recommendation on a case for the iPad Pro 10.5? I prefer a case that doesn’t add bulk, is easy to take on/off, and has a place for the Apple Pencil. I like the look of &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.padandquill.com/cases-for-ipad/oxford-leather-ipad-pro-105-case.html&quot;&gt;the Pad &amp;amp; Quill Oxford case&lt;/a&gt;, but I am uncertain about the adhesive tape and how easy it is to take the case off.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 May 2018 16:17:39 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/05/03/does-anyone-have.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/05/03/does-anyone-have.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;[flip.it/996yWZ](http://flip.it/996yWZ)
[flip.it/996yWZ](http://flip.it/996yWZ)&quot;&gt;Rick Dickinson, designer of Sinclair home computers, dies&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My first computer was the Timex Sinclair, which my grandmother bought for me when I was a junior in high school. It was important because provided access to a computer at an affordable price.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Apr 2018 16:06:31 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/04/28/rick-dickinson-designer.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/04/28/rick-dickinson-designer.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <title>Micro Blogging versus Social Networks</title>
        
        <description>&lt;p&gt;You might think it too fine a point, but I think any blogging product requires the ability to edit what one has written. To me, editing is a fundamental difference between blogging and social networks because blogging is about permanence where as the social network timeline/newsfeed is a black hole.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To me, what makes micro blogging different from social networks like Twitter is the permance I describe above, and therefore editing should be a fundamental requirement for all micro blogging apps.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 09:59:34 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/04/26/micro-blogging-versus.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/04/26/micro-blogging-versus.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Google releases a new Tasks app. It is a pretty barebones list making app that at least supports sub tasks. Unfortunately the iOS version is only for the iPhone and looks awful on the iPad, even the iPad Mini.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Apr 2018 20:05:09 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/04/25/google-releases-a.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/04/26/google-releases-a.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <title>Gmail versus Inbox</title>
        
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Google has released the new version of Gmail, which I am checking out. I have been using, and like, Inbox mostly because how quickly I can use it to triage email. By triage I mean browse for messages I want to read and then quickly archiving all the remaining messages. No other app, including Gmail provides as easy a way to archive a group of messages.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The downside of Inbox is that it is very JavaScript heavy and therefore the web app performance can suffer. Another downside is that the app versions don’t look as good on larger screens such as on my 10.5 iPad Pro in landscape.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, I am considering using Gmail on large screens and Inbox on small screens. However to decide that, I need to use the new Gmail for a while.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Apr 2018 12:49:47 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/04/25/gmail-versus-inbox.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/04/25/gmail-versus-inbox.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Did a little more investigation into &lt;a href=&quot;https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/04/22/i-got-a.html&quot;&gt;the watch face that Fossil “pushed” to my smart watch last weekend&lt;/a&gt;. What happens is, you receive a notification saying that you “unlocked” a face and whether you want to enable it. What I have found is that amongst the many faces that are pre-installed on the watch is one called Seasonal, and this is the face that Fossil pushes updates to. Consequently, Fossil is not consuming additional storage space on the watch with each “new face” as it is updating one face that is designed for different appearances, which in reality is how all faces work.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am wondering whether there is a Wear OS app that will automatically change watch faces I specify on a set schedule. I would like to rotate through some like the Outlook face that I like to use during the work day.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Apr 2018 09:27:04 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/04/25/did-a-little.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/04/25/did-a-little.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I use a simple process for telling whether my computer is working too hard, I listen for the fan. By this simple measure I determined that Chrome was just killing my computer and checking Process Explorer I did see high CPU utilization. I switched to Firefox as my primary browser and so far the fan has been quiet and the browser more responsive.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Apr 2018 09:16:39 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/04/25/i-use-a.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/04/25/i-use-a.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I use &lt;a href=&quot;https://aws.amazon.com/lightsail/&quot;&gt;Amazon Lightsail&lt;/a&gt; to host the Dockerized version of &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.monicahq.com/&quot;&gt;a CRM application&lt;/a&gt;. There has just been a major release and the latest version of the Docker image is not working for me. I take snapshots of the server as a back up, so I was able to revert back to the prior version of the server pretty easily. The process does involve creating a new instance from a snapshot, moving the public IP address to the new instance, and then deleting the old instance.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Apr 2018 09:07:15 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/04/25/i-use-amazon.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/04/25/i-use-amazon.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Do any of the other apps for micro.blog provide a way to edit posts?&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Apr 2018 20:44:01 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/04/23/do-any-of.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/04/24/do-any-of.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Really disappointing that we still cannot edit posts in the micro.blog app.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Apr 2018 20:33:15 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/04/23/really-disappointing-that.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/04/24/really-disappointing-that.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.washingtonpost.com/national/health-science/youve-been-given-a-terrible-diagnosis-heres-how-assess-your-survival-odds/2018/04/20/f46f14be-3699-11e8-8fd2-49fe3c675a89_story.html&quot;&gt;Washington Post: how to assess your survival odds&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Don’t expect stats to predict your future. And most important, live your life to the max.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Apr 2018 17:58:04 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/04/23/washington-post-how.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/04/23/washington-post-how.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;So, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.recode.net/2018/4/20/17264274/flickr-smugmug-yahoo-oath-verizon-deal-photo-sharing-service-mobile-instagram&quot;&gt;Flickr has been acquired by SmugMug&lt;/a&gt;. Pondering whether I want to keep my pics in Flicker and let them go along for the ride to SmugMug, or cut ties and only use Google Photos.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Apr 2018 14:10:04 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/04/23/so-flickr-has.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/04/23/so-flickr-has.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;People suggesting that Trump did something wrong by not attending the funeral for Barbara Bush might stop to consider whether he was invited by the Bushes.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 22 Apr 2018 15:41:08 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/04/22/people-suggesting-that.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/04/22/people-suggesting-that.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I got a Fossil Explorist Q, which is a Wear OS smart watch, for my birthday. Today Fossil pushed a face, commemorating Earth Day, to my watch, which was unexpected. Now I am curious to learn what other faces Fossil will push. I think this is a nice &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Easter_egg_(media)&quot;&gt;Easter egg&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 22 Apr 2018 15:35:42 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/04/22/i-got-a.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/04/22/i-got-a.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;All the way back on March 24, 2009  &lt;a href=&quot;https://fjmnotes.com/2009/03/14/time-to-take-off-the-shades/&quot;&gt;I wrote&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;when corporations own all mass media, how can we trust the news?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 19 Apr 2018 21:59:42 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/04/19/all-the-way.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/04/20/all-the-way.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://fjmnotes.com/2008/09/27/not-the-best-of-times/&quot;&gt;Back in September 2008&lt;/a&gt; I thought the United States was in the worst state of my life time. I was very wrong.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 19 Apr 2018 21:01:22 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/04/19/back-in-september.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/04/20/back-in-september.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Everything restored on the Pixel 2 except for the Android Wear settings, so now I have to factory reset my watches and completely reconfigure them to manage them in the Wear OS  app. What an awful user experience.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 19 Apr 2018 13:45:41 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/04/19/everything-restored-on.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/04/19/everything-restored-on.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Something really bad just happened to my Pixel 2 to shut down and then not boot. I have had to do a factory reset. Now restoring from backup. I had just downloaded the NASA picture of the day and was making it the wallpaper on the phone when this happened.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 19 Apr 2018 12:34:15 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/04/19/something-really-bad.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/04/19/something-really-bad.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.evernote.com/blog/2018/04/18/stacey-harmon-why-michael-hyatt-is-wrong-about-organizing-evernote-with-tags/&quot;&gt;Stacey Harmon: “Why Michael Hyatt is Wrong about Organizing Evernote with Tags”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;The right way for me — as well as the vast majority of the people I have coached over my years as an Evernote consultant — is by using notebooks and stacks as the primary organizing blocks of Evernote, with tags being used not as an organizational tool, but a find feature in Evernote.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have used Evernote for a long time, and I use notebooks and stacks as the primary organizational method and tags to help find information. When seek information in Evernote I usually search for that information across all notes unless I expect to only find it in a certain notebook or stack.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 18 Apr 2018 16:33:40 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/04/18/stacey-harmon-why.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/04/18/stacey-harmon-why.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.laptopmag.com/articles/every-ipad-keyboard-shortcut&quot;&gt;Best iPad Keyboard Shortcuts (for Smart Keyboards or Bluetooth)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;These keyboard shortcuts don’t require the Smart Keyboard or the iPad Pro. These tricks will work if you pair a Bluetooth keyboard with any iPad running iOS 9 or later.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 18 Apr 2018 16:24:08 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/04/18/best-ipad-keyboard.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/04/18/best-ipad-keyboard.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I have installed &lt;a href=&quot;http://getdrafts.com&quot;&gt;Drafts 5&lt;/a&gt;, purchased the yearly subscription, and I am now writing my first micro.blog post using it. Let’s see how well this works. Sent over to the micro.blog app where I can edit further. Of course, this method requires that you have the micro.blog app installed on your iPad, but you don’t have to generate a new app code for it to work.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 18 Apr 2018 16:08:51 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/04/18/i-have-installed.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/04/18/i-have-installed.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Yippee! I made it to 52!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 18 Apr 2018 11:28:04 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/04/18/yippee-i-made.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/04/18/yippee-i-made.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;After one day of full time usage, I am finding Firefox to be significantly faster than Chrome. One exception does seem to be with Inbox, which is heavy Javascript. I also may not have all of the Extensions installed in Firefox as I have in Chrome.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 17 Apr 2018 12:02:03 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/04/17/after-one-day.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/04/17/after-one-day.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mirroring360.com/&quot;&gt;Mirroring360&lt;/a&gt; looks like a useful addition to my toolbox. Found via &lt;a href=&quot;https://mmitii.mattballantine.com/2018/04/17/the-little-white-doo-dah-that-changed-my-working-life/amp/?__twitter_impression=true&quot;&gt;a blog post about the Apple Pencil&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 17 Apr 2018 09:25:40 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/04/17/mirroringhttpswwwmirroringcom-looks-like.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/04/17/mirroringhttpswwwmirroringcom-looks-like.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;At a minimum &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.washingtonpost.com/politics/trump-puts-the-brake-on-new-russian-sanctions-reversing-haleys-announcement/2018/04/16/ac3ad4f8-417f-11e8-8569-26fda6b404c7_story.html&quot;&gt;this looks incompetent&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 16 Apr 2018 17:02:45 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/04/16/at-a-minimum.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/04/16/at-a-minimum.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;It is really frustrating when applications don’t work the same way across platforms. Looking at you &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.lastpass.com&quot;&gt;Lastpass&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 16 Apr 2018 11:05:43 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/04/16/it-is-really.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/04/16/it-is-really.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;It might just be me, but it seems that Chrome is getting slower and slower. I’ve decided to start using Firefox for a while to see if the aggravation decreases.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 16 Apr 2018 09:37:35 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/04/16/it-might-just.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/04/16/it-might-just.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <title>Boycotts and Free Speech </title>
        
        <description>&lt;p&gt;What, if any, relationship is there between free speech and cable TV, and in particular news or opinion shows on cable TV? Cable TV is not the public square nor is it public airwaves, it is corporate owned and exists for the purposes of making money. The primary method for making money is advertising.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If people opt to make note of the advertisers and decide to not purchase products from those advertisers, which is known as boycotting their products, I don’t see how in any way that infringes on a person’s free speech rights. At most it infringes on that person’s ability to make money on cable TV.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Furthermore, free speech is a protection for citizens from government. If cable TV is not part of the government, then frankly I am not clear on what free speech rights apply to anything on cable TV. Claims about being “fair and balanced” is marketing and not statements of facts nor rights.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Apr 2018 10:59:50 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/04/13/boycotts-and-free.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/04/13/boycotts-and-free.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Google plans &lt;a href=&quot;https://9to5google.com/2018/04/11/gmail-web-revamp-leaks-w-rounded-design-sidebar-widgets-google-tasks-and-more/&quot;&gt;some interesting imorovements&lt;/a&gt; to Gmail. I am one of the few people who use Inbox because it enables me to quickly triage my email.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 22:09:37 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/04/11/google-plans-some.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/04/12/google-plans-some.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;One of the most &lt;a href=&quot;https://chromeunboxed.com/news/chrome-os-container-crostini-vscode-virtual-machine&quot;&gt;intriguing developments&lt;/a&gt; is containers in Chrome OS, particularly what &lt;a href=&quot;https://dropletcomputing.com/&quot;&gt;Droplet Comouting&lt;/a&gt; is doing.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 21:37:37 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/04/11/one-of-the.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/04/12/one-of-the.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I wish that telemarketing / telephone advertising were illegal. My landline is basically a telemarketing honey pot and my cellular number is becoming the same.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 16:16:22 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/04/11/201622.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/04/11/201622.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I wonder, back in the day, how many articles were written to explain Facebook and Twitter to people and convince them to use it? I am thinking that if someone has to write &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cultofmac.com/540623/quit-facebook-twitter/&quot;&gt;an article to explain a social network&lt;/a&gt;, it’s too complicated and will not draw lots of people. (Exhibit A: Google+)&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 09:19:26 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/04/11/i-wonder-back.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/04/11/i-wonder-back.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://time.com/5231694/national-beer-day/&quot;&gt;Today in 1933&lt;/a&gt; the 18th Ammendment to the U.S. Constitution was repealed. It can be done. It’s also #NationalBeerDay.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 07 Apr 2018 11:09:08 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/04/07/today-in-httptimecomnationalbeerday.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/04/07/today-in-httptimecomnationalbeerday.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.kickstarter.com/projects/413243358/mugsy-the-open-source-robotic-coffee-maker&quot;&gt;Mugsy is a robotic coffee maker&lt;/a&gt; with a Raspberry Pi brain.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 02 Apr 2018 17:50:30 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/04/02/mugsy-is-a.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/04/02/mugsy-is-a.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;What has changed since &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.govtech.com/education/What-Went-Wrong-with-LA-Unifieds-iPad-Program.html&quot;&gt;the L.A. public schools iPad program failed&lt;/a&gt;?&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 27 Mar 2018 13:14:11 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/03/27/what-has-changed.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/03/27/what-has-changed.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Is anger easy to &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.psychologytoday.com/us/blog/communication-success/201510/14-signs-psychological-and-emotional-manipulation&quot;&gt;manipulate&lt;/a&gt;?&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 26 Mar 2018 14:12:19 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/03/26/is-anger-easy.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/03/26/is-anger-easy.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;At what point does partisanship become out of control emotions?&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 26 Mar 2018 14:09:02 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/03/26/at-what-point.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/03/26/at-what-point.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Google Assistant is still flawed by not enabling users to specify unique trigger words for each device. So, I use my smartphone as an alarm clock and I thought it would be cool to enable &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.digitaltrends.com/home/google-assistant-routines/&quot;&gt;the Bedtime routine&lt;/a&gt; that turns down the phone, sets an alarm and shuts off lights.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Problem is that routine is enabled for Home and my Pixel phone. So, if I initiate the routine with the two in the same room, Home takes over and then sets the alarm for itself rather than on my phone.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, I think Google needs to do two things. First, it should provide a way to associate specific routines to specific assistant-enabled devices. Second, it needs to provide a way for users to create trigger words that are specific to devices. Right now, I can squeeze to trigger assistant on my phone and then start the routine, but that requires me to remember this rather than assistant being smart enough to remember for me.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Mar 2018 14:47:35 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/03/23/google-assistant-is.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/03/23/google-assistant-is.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;The scariest part of &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.npr.org/2018/03/22/594363877/trump-names-john-bolton-as-national-security-adviser&quot;&gt;the shrinking of President Trump’s echo chamber&lt;/a&gt; is that it increases the need for Congress to do it’s part to uphold and defend the constitution by putting country before party.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are closer to war today than we were yesterday.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Mar 2018 10:12:37 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/03/23/the-scariest-part.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/03/23/the-scariest-part.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.phoronix.com/scan.php?page=article&amp;amp;item=raspberrypi-3-bplus&amp;amp;num=1&quot;&gt;Here is a complete run down&lt;/a&gt; on the Raspberry Pi 3 B+ benchmarks.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 22 Mar 2018 16:14:20 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/03/22/here-is-a.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/03/22/here-is-a.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/brentsimmons/status/976528016594558976&quot;&gt;This tweet&lt;/a&gt; by @inessential touches on what I think is a root of many problems in the United States. You might say the problem is immaturity, but it is worse than that, the problem is that we have de-valued maturity. Maturity is a life-long process and with it comes the wisdom to know that one does not, cannot, know everything and therefore is open to changing their mind.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 22 Mar 2018 11:09:47 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/03/22/this-tweethttpstwittercombrentsimmonsstatus-by.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/03/22/this-tweethttpstwittercombrentsimmonsstatus-by.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I think the fact that I can’t find who I am following on Micro.blog is a real gap. A tip to fill the gap is to favorite at least one post of each person you follow.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 22 Mar 2018 11:03:12 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/03/22/i-think-the.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/03/22/i-think-the.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.newyorker.com/magazine/2018/03/26/the-gun-owners-of-the-parkland-generation?mbid=social_twitter&quot;&gt;Gun Country: A new generation of American kids embraces firearms&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The key thing to take note of in the story above is the relationships between the parents and children and the teaching. Now here is the problem, not every child has such relationships or teaching.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 22 Mar 2018 09:10:38 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/03/22/gun-country-a.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/03/22/gun-country-a.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I received the new &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.raspberrypi.org/blog/raspberry-pi-3-model-bplus-sale-now-35/&quot;&gt;Raspberry Pi 3 B+&lt;/a&gt; that became available on Pi day. This new model has a faster processor and faster networking, and in my experience with it today I find it to be noticably faster as a desktop.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 21 Mar 2018 21:04:10 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/03/21/i-received-the.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/03/22/i-received-the.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;To those who are smarter than me. If I don’t have a VPN tunnel from end-to-end, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.wired.com/story/alphabet-outline-vpn-software/&quot;&gt;why should I use a VPN solution like the one Google is proposing&lt;/a&gt;? At some point my data is still traversing the internet unprotected.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 21 Mar 2018 14:27:20 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/03/21/to-those-who.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/03/21/to-those-who.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.nytimes.com/2018/03/19/opinion/facebook-cambridge-analytica.html&quot;&gt;It ought to be clear&lt;/a&gt; by now that we need a form of &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/General_Data_Protection_Regulation&quot;&gt;GDPR&lt;/a&gt; in the United States. We might need something stronger.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 20 Mar 2018 09:47:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/03/20/it-ought-to.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/03/20/it-ought-to.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;In the past we had some consensus on what is right and wrong, and at the very least agreement that right and wrong is important. The problem is right and wrong is no longer important, nor the point, instead that has been replaced with, you are either with me or against me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You cannot solve any problem if your starting position is effectively, we will solve that problem only if everyone agrees with me.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 19 Mar 2018 13:33:43 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/03/19/in-the-past.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/03/19/in-the-past.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;On the way home last night from a gathering of friends in Royal Oak, I stopped at a store and found some &lt;a href=&quot;https://foundersbrewing.com/our-beer/kbs/&quot;&gt;Founders KBS&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.atwaterbeer.com/beer-type/berry-cobbler-ale/#&quot;&gt;Atwaters Blueberry Cobbler&lt;/a&gt; for sale. The store owner started the day with 12 cases of KBS and had 2 left by 8:30 PM and will probably be sold out by this afternoon. Right place, right time for me.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2018 09:25:56 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/03/15/on-the-way.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/03/15/on-the-way.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I am not excited by subtle UI design changes such as being shown by &lt;a href=&quot;https://arstechnica.com/gadgets/2018/03/hands-on-with-android-p-is-this-the-beginning-of-a-new-design-language/&quot;&gt;the Android P developer preview&lt;/a&gt;. What I am more interested in is substantial changes, which frankly have been few and far between in Android and iOS. I bought a Pixel 2 last year only because I knew with the release of Android O the Nexus 6P had reached the end of the line and would get no more updates. Otherwise, the 6P was and still is a great phone.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2018 09:17:57 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/03/15/i-am-not.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/03/15/i-am-not.html</guid>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
