<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Frank McPherson</title>
    <description>Follow &lt;a href=&quot;https://micro.blog/frankm&quot;&gt;@frankm on Micro.blog&lt;/a&gt;.</description>
    <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/</link>
    <pubDate>Sat, 19 May 2018 10:25:04 -0400</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 19 May 2018 10:25:04 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;For the last couple of weeks I have been using &lt;a href=&quot;https://noteplan.co/&quot;&gt;NotePlan&lt;/a&gt;, and I think what I like most about it is that you end up with a daily log of what you did. &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.foldingtext.com/&quot;&gt;FoldingText&lt;/a&gt; looks like a similarly useful tool, but not available on iOS, but I like outliners. The feature I want in an outliner is simple linking both with an outline file and to external items.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 19 May 2018 10:25:01 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/05/19/for-the-last.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/05/19/for-the-last.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;The best thing about micro.blog is that it’s just people. When you browse through Discover, you are discovering people.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 19 May 2018 10:09:44 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/05/19/the-best-thing.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/05/19/the-best-thing.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;It seems to me that the majority of school shootings have occurred at public schools. Am I wrong?&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 May 2018 14:53:38 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/05/18/it-seems-to.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/05/18/it-seems-to.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Because I am an introvert, emotionally-charged meetings, even if I am not the target of the emotion, is very draining. Today was one of those days, being remedied by guacamole and a &lt;a href=&quot;https://foundersbrewing.com/our-beer/dankwood/&quot;&gt;Dankwood&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 17 May 2018 20:11:11 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/05/17/because-i-am.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/05/18/because-i-am.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;One of the most surprising things I’ve learned about myself during the last three years is that I like guacamole.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 17 May 2018 19:56:52 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/05/17/235652.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/05/17/235652.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;The Cubs lost another game to the Braves. The Braves look for real.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 16 May 2018 22:31:22 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/05/16/the-cubs-lost.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/05/17/the-cubs-lost.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Is there a way to disable iOS predictive text when using an external keyboard?&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 14 May 2018 09:05:47 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/05/14/130547.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/05/14/130547.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Chrome OS’ forthcoming &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.xda-developers.com/linux-apps-chrome-os-overview-crostini/&quot;&gt;ability to run Linux apps&lt;/a&gt; appears to me to mostly be something Google did so that their engineers could actually use the Pixelbook. Once that feature is seen in the code you might as well let the broad developer community in on the fun.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The question is whether regular users will benefit from this feature. Most likely not if nothing more than the actual number of Linux apps a “regular user” might find useful are limited. Right now I can only think one app I will want to run in such a container and that is &lt;a href=&quot;https://standardnotes.org&quot;&gt;Standard Notes&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 13 May 2018 13:05:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/05/13/chrome-os-forthcoming.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/05/13/chrome-os-forthcoming.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;My Fossil Q Explorist now talks.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 13 May 2018 12:54:51 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/05/13/my-fossil-q.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/05/13/my-fossil-q.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;A credit card company &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.theverge.com/2018/3/6/17071478/spam-calls-how-to-stop-block-robocalls-robots-scam-iphone-android&quot;&gt;robot keeps calling my smart phone&lt;/a&gt; and neither Google nor &lt;a href=&quot;https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.nomorobo&amp;amp;hl=en_US&quot;&gt;Nomorobo&lt;/a&gt; is able to catch it because each call is from a different number and often local. Right now, if caller ID doesn’t show something I recognize, I don’t answer the phone.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I personally think we need to outlaw phone calling robots, before &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.theverge.com/2018/5/9/17335710/google-duplex-phone-call-ai-assistant-service-industry&quot;&gt;Google Duplex&lt;/a&gt; gets entrenched.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 May 2018 12:03:45 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/05/10/a-credit-card.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/05/10/a-credit-card.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.theverge.com/2018/5/8/17333154/googe-lens-ai-ar-live-demo-hands-on-io-2018&quot;&gt;Google Lens actually shows how AI can make life easier - The Verge&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I just would like Lens to tell me what type of bird I took a picture of in Bermuda.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 08 May 2018 21:33:46 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/05/08/google-lens-actually.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/05/09/google-lens-actually.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Do we want our devices to become nannies? I get why Google and Microsoft are reacting to reports on the addictive nature of the devices, but it seems to me we need to learn self control and not rely on external influence to tell us what and what not to do.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 08 May 2018 20:08:38 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/05/08/do-we-want.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/05/09/do-we-want.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <title>Drafts or Ulysses?</title>
        
        <description>&lt;p&gt;One thing I find frustrating about iOS are the number of apps that all seem to do the exact same thing. How do you decide on one over the other? An example is Drafts and Ulysses, both are good markdown editors but Drafts supports more automation. Last summer I was looking for a new editor and Ulysses came highly recommended, so I bought it, but then the company switched to a subscription model and that turned me off, I decided to not buy in to the subscription.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then I learned about Drafts, and so I went and downloaded it and have used it to write some blog posts. To date I have mostly used it to write long posts for &lt;a href=&quot;http://writing.frankmcpherson.org&quot;&gt;one site&lt;/a&gt; that only has a “basic” web-based editor. Of course, Drafts has now been recently upgraded and it too has a subscription model.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To me, it doesn’t make sense to have Ulysses and Drafts on my iPad, Drafts seems to able to do the job good enough. However, so far I have not seen an Action for sending text to Wordpress, which I find a bit surprising. Does anyone know of such an Action? The one in the Drafts directory appears to require components not part of Wordpress.com.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 08 May 2018 10:54:05 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/05/08/drafts-or-ulysses.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/05/08/drafts-or-ulysses.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.detroitnews.com/story/sports/columnists/bob-wojnowski/2018/05/07/wojo-detroit-pga-tour-quicken-loans/34670853/&quot;&gt;Wojo: PGA Tour’s first stop in Detroit is another ace in city’s revival&lt;/a&gt;. It’s a bit hard to imagine, but great news for Detroit, none the less.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 07 May 2018 21:58:12 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/05/07/wojo-pga-tours.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/05/08/wojo-pga-tours.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;The Cubs &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mlbtraderumors.com/2018/05/cubs-place-yu-darvish-on-10-day-dl.html&quot;&gt;put Yu Darvish on the 10-day DL&lt;/a&gt; for the flu?!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 07 May 2018 20:20:52 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/05/07/the-cubs-put.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/05/08/the-cubs-put.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I used some credit card reward to discount the cost of the Pad &amp;amp; Quill case for th iPad Pro 10.5 that &lt;a href=&quot;http://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/05/03/does-anyone-have.html&quot;&gt;I wrote about earlier&lt;/a&gt;. The case arrived today and it is beautiful and provides plenty of protection but also adds bulk. It is going to take time for the leather to break in, so the race is between the breakin of the leather or me.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 07 May 2018 17:30:05 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/05/07/i-used-some.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/05/07/i-used-some.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Updates to Google Assistant are &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.blog.google/products/wear-os/get-more-done-google-assistant-wear-os-google/?utm_source=tw&amp;amp;utm_medium=feed&amp;amp;utm_campaign=og&quot;&gt;coming to Wear OS.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 07 May 2018 17:15:50 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/05/07/updates-to-google.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/05/07/updates-to-google.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Watching the Cubs play the Cardinals. So far two calls have been overturned by replay. Replay is showing how bad baseball umpires are, you can almost say something like 25% of all calls made in MLB history before replay were wrong.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 05 May 2018 15:18:06 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/05/05/watching-the-cubs.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/05/05/watching-the-cubs.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Does anyone have a recommendation on a case for the iPad Pro 10.5? I prefer a case that doesn’t add bulk, is easy to take on/off, and has a place for the Apple Pencil. I like the look of &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.padandquill.com/cases-for-ipad/oxford-leather-ipad-pro-105-case.html&quot;&gt;the Pad &amp;amp; Quill Oxford case&lt;/a&gt;, but I am uncertain about the adhesive tape and how easy it is to take the case off.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 03 May 2018 16:17:39 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/05/03/does-anyone-have.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/05/03/does-anyone-have.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;[flip.it/996yWZ](http://flip.it/996yWZ)
[flip.it/996yWZ](http://flip.it/996yWZ)&quot;&gt;Rick Dickinson, designer of Sinclair home computers, dies&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My first computer was the Timex Sinclair, which my grandmother bought for me when I was a junior in high school. It was important because provided access to a computer at an affordable price.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Apr 2018 16:06:31 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/04/28/rick-dickinson-designer.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/04/28/rick-dickinson-designer.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <title>Micro Blogging versus Social Networks</title>
        
        <description>&lt;p&gt;You might think it too fine a point, but I think any blogging product requires the ability to edit what one has written. To me, editing is a fundamental difference between blogging and social networks because blogging is about permanence where as the social network timeline/newsfeed is a black hole.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To me, what makes micro blogging different from social networks like Twitter is the permance I describe above, and therefore editing should be a fundamental requirement for all micro blogging apps.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2018 09:59:34 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/04/26/micro-blogging-versus.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/04/26/micro-blogging-versus.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Google releases a new Tasks app. It is a pretty barebones list making app that at least supports sub tasks. Unfortunately the iOS version is only for the iPhone and looks awful on the iPad, even the iPad Mini.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Apr 2018 20:05:09 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/04/25/google-releases-a.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/04/26/google-releases-a.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <title>Gmail versus Inbox</title>
        
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Google has released the new version of Gmail, which I am checking out. I have been using, and like, Inbox mostly because how quickly I can use it to triage email. By triage I mean browse for messages I want to read and then quickly archiving all the remaining messages. No other app, including Gmail provides as easy a way to archive a group of messages.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The downside of Inbox is that it is very JavaScript heavy and therefore the web app performance can suffer. Another downside is that the app versions don’t look as good on larger screens such as on my 10.5 iPad Pro in landscape.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, I am considering using Gmail on large screens and Inbox on small screens. However to decide that, I need to use the new Gmail for a while.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Apr 2018 12:49:47 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/04/25/gmail-versus-inbox.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/04/25/gmail-versus-inbox.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Did a little more investigation into &lt;a href=&quot;https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/04/22/i-got-a.html&quot;&gt;the watch face that Fossil “pushed” to my smart watch last weekend&lt;/a&gt;. What happens is, you receive a notification saying that you “unlocked” a face and whether you want to enable it. What I have found is that amongst the many faces that are pre-installed on the watch is one called Seasonal, and this is the face that Fossil pushes updates to. Consequently, Fossil is not consuming additional storage space on the watch with each “new face” as it is updating one face that is designed for different appearances, which in reality is how all faces work.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am wondering whether there is a Wear OS app that will automatically change watch faces I specify on a set schedule. I would like to rotate through some like the Outlook face that I like to use during the work day.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Apr 2018 09:27:04 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/04/25/did-a-little.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/04/25/did-a-little.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I use a simple process for telling whether my computer is working too hard, I listen for the fan. By this simple measure I determined that Chrome was just killing my computer and checking Process Explorer I did see high CPU utilization. I switched to Firefox as my primary browser and so far the fan has been quiet and the browser more responsive.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Apr 2018 09:16:39 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/04/25/i-use-a.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/04/25/i-use-a.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I use &lt;a href=&quot;https://aws.amazon.com/lightsail/&quot;&gt;Amazon Lightsail&lt;/a&gt; to host the Dockerized version of &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.monicahq.com/&quot;&gt;a CRM application&lt;/a&gt;. There has just been a major release and the latest version of the Docker image is not working for me. I take snapshots of the server as a back up, so I was able to revert back to the prior version of the server pretty easily. The process does involve creating a new instance from a snapshot, moving the public IP address to the new instance, and then deleting the old instance.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Apr 2018 09:07:15 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/04/25/i-use-amazon.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/04/25/i-use-amazon.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Do any of the other apps for micro.blog provide a way to edit posts?&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Apr 2018 20:44:01 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/04/23/do-any-of.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/04/24/do-any-of.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Really disappointing that we still cannot edit posts in the micro.blog app.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Apr 2018 20:33:15 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/04/23/really-disappointing-that.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/04/24/really-disappointing-that.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.washingtonpost.com/national/health-science/youve-been-given-a-terrible-diagnosis-heres-how-assess-your-survival-odds/2018/04/20/f46f14be-3699-11e8-8fd2-49fe3c675a89_story.html&quot;&gt;Washington Post: how to assess your survival odds&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Don’t expect stats to predict your future. And most important, live your life to the max.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Apr 2018 17:58:04 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/04/23/washington-post-how.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/04/23/washington-post-how.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;So, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.recode.net/2018/4/20/17264274/flickr-smugmug-yahoo-oath-verizon-deal-photo-sharing-service-mobile-instagram&quot;&gt;Flickr has been acquired by SmugMug&lt;/a&gt;. Pondering whether I want to keep my pics in Flicker and let them go along for the ride to SmugMug, or cut ties and only use Google Photos.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Apr 2018 14:10:04 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/04/23/so-flickr-has.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/04/23/so-flickr-has.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;People suggesting that Trump did something wrong by not attending the funeral for Barbara Bush might stop to consider whether he was invited by the Bushes.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 22 Apr 2018 15:41:08 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/04/22/people-suggesting-that.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/04/22/people-suggesting-that.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I got a Fossil Explorist Q, which is a Wear OS smart watch, for my birthday. Today Fossil pushed a face, commemorating Earth Day, to my watch, which was unexpected. Now I am curious to learn what other faces Fossil will push. I think this is a nice &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Easter_egg_(media)&quot;&gt;Easter egg&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 22 Apr 2018 15:35:42 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/04/22/i-got-a.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/04/22/i-got-a.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;All the way back on March 24, 2009  &lt;a href=&quot;https://fjmnotes.com/2009/03/14/time-to-take-off-the-shades/&quot;&gt;I wrote&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;when corporations own all mass media, how can we trust the news?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 19 Apr 2018 21:59:42 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/04/19/all-the-way.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/04/20/all-the-way.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://fjmnotes.com/2008/09/27/not-the-best-of-times/&quot;&gt;Back in September 2008&lt;/a&gt; I thought the United States was in the worst state of my life time. I was very wrong.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 19 Apr 2018 21:01:22 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/04/19/back-in-september.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/04/20/back-in-september.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Everything restored on the Pixel 2 except for the Android Wear settings, so now I have to factory reset my watches and completely reconfigure them to manage them in the Wear OS  app. What an awful user experience.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 19 Apr 2018 13:45:41 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/04/19/everything-restored-on.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/04/19/everything-restored-on.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Something really bad just happened to my Pixel 2 to shut down and then not boot. I have had to do a factory reset. Now restoring from backup. I had just downloaded the NASA picture of the day and was making it the wallpaper on the phone when this happened.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 19 Apr 2018 12:34:15 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/04/19/something-really-bad.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/04/19/something-really-bad.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.evernote.com/blog/2018/04/18/stacey-harmon-why-michael-hyatt-is-wrong-about-organizing-evernote-with-tags/&quot;&gt;Stacey Harmon: “Why Michael Hyatt is Wrong about Organizing Evernote with Tags”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;The right way for me — as well as the vast majority of the people I have coached over my years as an Evernote consultant — is by using notebooks and stacks as the primary organizing blocks of Evernote, with tags being used not as an organizational tool, but a find feature in Evernote.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have used Evernote for a long time, and I use notebooks and stacks as the primary organizational method and tags to help find information. When seek information in Evernote I usually search for that information across all notes unless I expect to only find it in a certain notebook or stack.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 18 Apr 2018 16:33:40 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/04/18/stacey-harmon-why.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/04/18/stacey-harmon-why.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.laptopmag.com/articles/every-ipad-keyboard-shortcut&quot;&gt;Best iPad Keyboard Shortcuts (for Smart Keyboards or Bluetooth)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;These keyboard shortcuts don’t require the Smart Keyboard or the iPad Pro. These tricks will work if you pair a Bluetooth keyboard with any iPad running iOS 9 or later.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 18 Apr 2018 16:24:08 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/04/18/best-ipad-keyboard.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/04/18/best-ipad-keyboard.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I have installed &lt;a href=&quot;http://getdrafts.com&quot;&gt;Drafts 5&lt;/a&gt;, purchased the yearly subscription, and I am now writing my first micro.blog post using it. Let’s see how well this works. Sent over to the micro.blog app where I can edit further. Of course, this method requires that you have the micro.blog app installed on your iPad, but you don’t have to generate a new app code for it to work.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 18 Apr 2018 16:08:51 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/04/18/i-have-installed.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/04/18/i-have-installed.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Yippee! I made it to 52!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 18 Apr 2018 11:28:04 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/04/18/yippee-i-made.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/04/18/yippee-i-made.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;After one day of full time usage, I am finding Firefox to be significantly faster than Chrome. One exception does seem to be with Inbox, which is heavy Javascript. I also may not have all of the Extensions installed in Firefox as I have in Chrome.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 17 Apr 2018 12:02:03 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/04/17/after-one-day.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/04/17/after-one-day.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.mirroring360.com/&quot;&gt;Mirroring360&lt;/a&gt; looks like a useful addition to my toolbox. Found via &lt;a href=&quot;https://mmitii.mattballantine.com/2018/04/17/the-little-white-doo-dah-that-changed-my-working-life/amp/?__twitter_impression=true&quot;&gt;a blog post about the Apple Pencil&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 17 Apr 2018 09:25:40 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/04/17/mirroringhttpswwwmirroringcom-looks-like.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/04/17/mirroringhttpswwwmirroringcom-looks-like.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;At a minimum &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.washingtonpost.com/politics/trump-puts-the-brake-on-new-russian-sanctions-reversing-haleys-announcement/2018/04/16/ac3ad4f8-417f-11e8-8569-26fda6b404c7_story.html&quot;&gt;this looks incompetent&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 16 Apr 2018 17:02:45 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/04/16/at-a-minimum.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/04/16/at-a-minimum.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;It is really frustrating when applications don’t work the same way across platforms. Looking at you &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.lastpass.com&quot;&gt;Lastpass&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 16 Apr 2018 11:05:43 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/04/16/it-is-really.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/04/16/it-is-really.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;It might just be me, but it seems that Chrome is getting slower and slower. I’ve decided to start using Firefox for a while to see if the aggravation decreases.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 16 Apr 2018 09:37:35 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/04/16/it-might-just.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/04/16/it-might-just.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <title>Boycotts and Free Speech </title>
        
        <description>&lt;p&gt;What, if any, relationship is there between free speech and cable TV, and in particular news or opinion shows on cable TV? Cable TV is not the public square nor is it public airwaves, it is corporate owned and exists for the purposes of making money. The primary method for making money is advertising.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If people opt to make note of the advertisers and decide to not purchase products from those advertisers, which is known as boycotting their products, I don’t see how in any way that infringes on a person’s free speech rights. At most it infringes on that person’s ability to make money on cable TV.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Furthermore, free speech is a protection for citizens from government. If cable TV is not part of the government, then frankly I am not clear on what free speech rights apply to anything on cable TV. Claims about being “fair and balanced” is marketing and not statements of facts nor rights.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 13 Apr 2018 10:59:50 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/04/13/boycotts-and-free.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/04/13/boycotts-and-free.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Google plans &lt;a href=&quot;https://9to5google.com/2018/04/11/gmail-web-revamp-leaks-w-rounded-design-sidebar-widgets-google-tasks-and-more/&quot;&gt;some interesting imorovements&lt;/a&gt; to Gmail. I am one of the few people who use Inbox because it enables me to quickly triage my email.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 22:09:37 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/04/11/google-plans-some.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/04/12/google-plans-some.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;One of the most &lt;a href=&quot;https://chromeunboxed.com/news/chrome-os-container-crostini-vscode-virtual-machine&quot;&gt;intriguing developments&lt;/a&gt; is containers in Chrome OS, particularly what &lt;a href=&quot;https://dropletcomputing.com/&quot;&gt;Droplet Comouting&lt;/a&gt; is doing.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 21:37:37 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/04/11/one-of-the.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/04/12/one-of-the.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I wish that telemarketing / telephone advertising were illegal. My landline is basically a telemarketing honey pot and my cellular number is becoming the same.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 16:16:22 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/04/11/201622.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/04/11/201622.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I wonder, back in the day, how many articles were written to explain Facebook and Twitter to people and convince them to use it? I am thinking that if someone has to write &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cultofmac.com/540623/quit-facebook-twitter/&quot;&gt;an article to explain a social network&lt;/a&gt;, it’s too complicated and will not draw lots of people. (Exhibit A: Google+)&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 09:19:26 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/04/11/i-wonder-back.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/04/11/i-wonder-back.html</guid>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
