<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Frank McPherson</title>
    <description>Follow &lt;a href=&quot;https://micro.blog/frankm&quot;&gt;@frankm on Micro.blog&lt;/a&gt;.</description>
    <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/</link>
    <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jul 2018 14:19:33 -0400</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Jul 2018 14:19:33 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://artshow.scripting.com/&quot;&gt;artshow.scripting.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What art at the link above.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jul 2018 14:19:26 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/07/01/artshowscriptingcom-what-art.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/07/01/artshowscriptingcom-what-art.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <title>Blogging Since 1999</title>
        
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I’ve &lt;a href=&quot;https://writing.frankmcpherson.net/stories/2018/06/30/my-internet-writing-story.html&quot;&gt;ported a blog post I wrote in 2014 using Fargo to the site I am setting up&lt;/a&gt; using Jekyll and Netlify. The post is an historical account, current at that time, of the tools I used to write and host content on the web. I’ve been blogging since 1999, which means I am approaching 20 years of blogging.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Unfortunately, not all of my early content, almost 8 years worth, is accessible due to how that content was stored. However, there is access to the last decade worth of my writing, some of it good, most of it meh. I’ve &lt;a href=&quot;https://writing.frankmcpherson.net/about/&quot;&gt;pointed to the sites hosting those last 7 years&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jun 2018 18:30:04 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/06/30/blogging-since.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/06/30/blogging-since.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Looking back at &lt;a href=&quot;http://web.archive.org/web/20021016214953/http://fmcpherson.weblogger.com/2001/09/22&quot;&gt;another blog post I wrote after 9/11&lt;/a&gt;, and reflecting on the current state of the United States, I can’t help but wonder whether what is happening now is leading to a new generation of terrorists.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jun 2018 18:19:27 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/06/30/221927.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/06/30/221927.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Looking back at &lt;a href=&quot;http://web.archive.org/web/20020706073849/http://fmcpherson.weblogger.com/2001/09/15&quot;&gt;what I wrote 17 years ago after 9/11&lt;/a&gt;, as bad was it was then it would be hard to imagine then how things are now.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jun 2018 18:14:04 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/06/30/looking-back-at.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/06/30/looking-back-at.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.theverge.com/2018/6/29/17518582/microsoft-surface-dual-screen-andromeda-device-pocketable&quot;&gt;Microsoft details secret ‘pocketable’ Surface device in leaked email - The Verge&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What I find most intriguing about this leak is the idea of Microsoft inventing a new hardware category. Although, doesn’t a pocketable Surface device sound like a Pocket PC? I am not entirely sure I need a dual screen device, but something the size of an iPad Mini optimized for a stylus might get my money.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jun 2018 15:35:37 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/06/30/microsoft-details-secret.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/06/30/microsoft-details-secret.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Finished reading: &lt;a href=&quot;https://micro.blog/books/9780062291103&quot;&gt;WHEN SOCIETY BECOMES AN ADDICT&lt;/a&gt; by Anne Wilson Schaef, ISBN: 9780062291103 📚&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jun 2018 15:17:35 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/06/30/finished-reading-when.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/06/30/finished-reading-when.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Finished reading: Area 51: Redemption  by Bob Mayer&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jun 2018 15:05:23 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/06/30/finished-reading-area.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/06/30/finished-reading-area.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Currently reading: &lt;a href=&quot;https://micro.blog/books/9781633199323&quot;&gt;If These Walls Could Talk: Detroit Red Wings&lt;/a&gt; by Ken Daniels, ISBN: 9781633199323 📚&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jun 2018 14:58:44 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/06/30/185844.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/06/30/185844.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;It is 91 degrees out, 58% humidity, dew point 74 degrees. With the air conditioning going nearly full time, there is a ten degree difference between basement and top floor of our town house. Sitting in the basement watching a baseball game is too cold for shorts.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jun 2018 14:48:05 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/06/30/it-is-degrees.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/06/30/it-is-degrees.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Well, that was interesting. I updated my Pi3 with the latest release of Raspbian and then decided to clone my new Jekyll repo and edit &lt;a href=&quot;https://writing.frankmcpherson.net/about/&quot;&gt;the about page&lt;/a&gt; on my Raspberry Pi. Just because I could. I committed and pushed the update to the repo and checked the about page on the new site, and the new edits did not appear. Went to the Netlify site, logged in, and found the deploy failed with some error relating to node. I think during deploy nodejs 8 was attempted to be installed and it failed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Next, I tried a fresh re-deploy and selected clear cache and this time deployment was successful.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, what I learned here is that it appears whenever Netlify sees and pulls an update from the repo it seems to rebuild the container/VM that is hosting the site that includes installing nodejs, installing ruby gems (Jekyll uses ruby) then does a Jekyll build and ultimately deploys the site from the site fielder.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jun 2018 13:41:47 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/06/30/well-that-was.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/06/30/well-that-was.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://xn--sr8hvo.ws/&quot;&gt;Web rings&lt;/a&gt; are still a thing?&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jun 2018 12:09:51 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/06/30/web-rings-are.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/06/30/web-rings-are.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Via &lt;a href=&quot;http://scripting.com/2018/06/30.html#a140709&quot;&gt;Scripting News&lt;/a&gt;: “I don’t think any person should die because they are too poor to live.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sounds like a good Democrat party theme to me.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jun 2018 12:03:56 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/06/30/via-scripting-news.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/06/30/via-scripting-news.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <title>Long Form Writing and Trying Out Netlify</title>
        
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Unlike most others here at micro.blog, I consider &lt;a href=&quot;https://frankmcpherson.blog/&quot;&gt;my micro.blog&lt;/a&gt; as my blog. The reason is that I distinguish blogs from long form writing and publishing on the Internet. For me, a blog post is 1 to 3 paragraphs and written in about 15 minutes or less.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I blog to share a thought or something of interest to me, I write to formulate and share ideas.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When I set up my micro.blog account and associated a personal blog domain to it, I decided that I would use my then current blog, &lt;a href=&quot;http://writing.frankmcpherson.org&quot;&gt;Let’s Be Frank&lt;/a&gt;, for long form writing. The “broad” push to HTTPS is going to make that a problem because that blog is managed using an app written by Dave Winer called &lt;a href=&quot;http://1999.io&quot;&gt;1999.io&lt;/a&gt;, and it has a lot of Javascript libraries that I don’t think he is every going to convert to HTTPS.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, stay there and maybe figure out how to convert to HTTPS or look somewhere else? I recently &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.baty.net/2018/back-to-netlify/&quot;&gt;learned about Netlify from Jack Baty&lt;/a&gt; and after checking out its web site, I determined it has much of what I was looking for: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.netlify.com/pricing/&quot;&gt;low price&lt;/a&gt;, easy HTTPS implementation, and flexibility.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Netlify does not provide a Content Management System, but it integrates with Github to provide continuous deployment, so you can use static site generators like Jekyll for publishing content. Since I have a little experience with Jekyll, I decided to try out Netlify by following &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.netlify.com/blog/2015/10/28/a-step-by-step-guide-jekyll-3.0-on-netlify/&quot;&gt;their Jekyll tutorial&lt;/a&gt; and it didn’t take me long to get a site up and available via HTTPS.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The upside with the approach I have so far is that I can write and publish content from any device, particularly my iPad. All you really need to do is add a file in the proper naming format to the posts folder of your Github repository. I’ve cloned the repository to Working Copy on my iPad and found a Drafts action that will save a new item to Working Copy and insert the proper header informatation that Jekyll requires.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Right now &lt;a href=&quot;https://writing.frankmcpherson.net&quot;&gt;the new site&lt;/a&gt; is very much a work in progress and there may be changes. Oh, and I am aware of the irony of me writing this post here but this is is where you know me and I am not a stickler to such self determined rules.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jun 2018 11:38:04 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/06/30/long-form-writing.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/06/30/long-form-writing.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Got my invite to &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.blog.google/products/google-one/one-simple-way-get-more-out-google/&quot;&gt;Google One&lt;/a&gt; today, which I’ve accepted although I am not sure of the point.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jun 2018 11:58:47 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/06/26/got-my-invite.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/06/26/got-my-invite.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;The bridge freeway oasis is unique to the Chicago area and is &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.chicagotribune.com/news/ct-met-ohare-oasis-tollway-expansion-met-20180622-story.html#nws=true&quot;&gt;slowly being removed.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jun 2018 08:44:14 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/06/25/the-bridge-freeway.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/06/25/the-bridge-freeway.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://frankmcpherson.blog/uploads/2018/a80a662dc8.jpg&quot; width=&quot;600&quot; height=&quot;600&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 24 Jun 2018 21:37:06 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/06/24/013706.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/06/25/013706.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Do you think of micro.blog as a blog or an alternative to Twitter?&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 24 Jun 2018 15:07:29 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/06/24/do-you-think.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/06/24/do-you-think.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Greatness is neither self determined nor self declared.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jun 2018 10:36:13 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/06/21/greatness-is-neither.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/06/21/greatness-is-neither.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I’ve got Android Messages for Web enabled and I found that it does work with Chrome on iOS, however I haven’t received notifications for new in-bound messages on iOS. You can also set up Messages for Web with multiple computers but only one can be active at a time. I have to admit, this seems to work pretty well and helps me get past a limitation with Pushbullet on iOS.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jun 2018 17:53:22 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/06/20/ive-got-android.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/06/20/ive-got-android.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;If we can’t agree that there are things humans should not do to other humans, particularly to those who are vulnerable, then we have a problem and that is being exposed in the United States’ &lt;a href=&quot;https://slate.com/news-and-politics/2018/06/how-the-trump-administration-is-defending-its-indefensible-child-separation-policy.html&quot;&gt;current practice of separating children from families&lt;/a&gt;. From the time that Trump seriously started running for president we have seen a widening gulf between those who care about what we do to one another and those who do not.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jun 2018 09:20:40 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/06/20/if-we-cant.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/06/20/if-we-cant.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I don’t get the need for &lt;a href=&quot;https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.google.android.apps.podcasts&quot;&gt;Google Podcasts&lt;/a&gt;. There is already a section for Podcasts in Google Play Music that I have been using and have subscriptions. Google Podcasts isn’t even smart enough to import my existing subscriptions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don’t listen to many podcasts any more now that I don’t spend an hour a day in the car commuting to an office.  In fact, most of my recent podcast listening has been using Apple’s Podcast app on an iPad.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jun 2018 14:18:33 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/06/19/i-dont-get.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/06/19/i-dont-get.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I am curious to know whether &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.zdnet.com/article/googles-android-messages-for-web-is-here-this-is-how-it-lets-you-text-from-pcs-macs&quot;&gt;the new web messenging feature of Android Messages&lt;/a&gt; will work in a browser on an iPad. I’ve been using Pushbullet for this type of remote texting, and that works well from an Android tablet or Windows PC, but the iOS version of Pushbullet does not support SMS.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jun 2018 14:08:19 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/06/19/i-am-curious.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/06/19/i-am-curious.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I’ve been hanging out at the new Starbucks down the road from my house.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://frankmcpherson.blog/uploads/2018/9069db1e4a.jpg&quot; width=&quot;600&quot; height=&quot;599&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 16 Jun 2018 17:00:09 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/06/16/ive-been-hanging.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/06/16/ive-been-hanging.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I think I know what happened. With previous posts I published from Ulysses I did not enable markdown in the publishing dialog and therefore the publisher converted the markdown to HTML so it appeared correct in Wordpress. In the previous post I enabled markdown, and since Wordpress was not configured to use markdown it did not render properly. So, to have enabled markdown in the writing settings of the WP-Admin console, which fixed the problem.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In other words…. operator error! :)&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 16 Jun 2018 15:59:22 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/06/16/195922.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/06/16/195922.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I just published &lt;a href=&quot;https://the-narthex.org/2018/06/16/daryl-madden-unlearn/&quot;&gt;a post on one of my Wordpress blogs&lt;/a&gt; using Ulysses for iOS, which I have used to publish before, and for some reason the markdown for hyperlinks was not properly recognized. Does anyone know if something has changed with Wordpress?&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 16 Jun 2018 15:37:11 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/06/16/i-just-published.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/06/16/i-just-published.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;It is really disappointing that Apple removed all handwriting recognition keyboards for iOS. I would really like to be able to use the Apple Pencil in all of apps, which I should be able to at least do with a HWR keyboard. It looks like MyScript Stack and Stylus were all removed from the store.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jun 2018 10:02:21 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/06/15/140221.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/06/15/140221.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <title>The Overthrow Will Not Be By Force.</title>
        
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Too many people in the United States think our government will be overthrown by force when the reality is it is happening in just the opposite manner. The strong arguments against gun control in the U.S. is evidence of this, as the argument centers around needing to keep guns as protection against government oppression. The powers that be don’t need to take guns away, they just need us to keep arguing about them, which fossilizes idealogy and keeps attention away from what is really happening.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The constitution enables authoritarianism when Congress and the Supreme Court do not function in their jobs as overseers of the Presidency. When Congress and the Supreme Court simply align with a president due to party affliation, you have a dictator in practice.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today the process nearly complete, and gerrymandering will seal the deal. Gerrymandering removes the one power citizens have, which is to vote. You don’t need to burn down the flag nor rip up the Constitution, all that is needed is idealogical compliance to what the Presidency wants.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jun 2018 11:01:33 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/06/13/the-overthrow-will.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/06/13/the-overthrow-will.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.computerworld.com/article/3278560/mobile-apps/ios-apps-on-mac.html&quot;&gt;www.computerworld.com&lt;/a&gt; also takes note of the similarities, and differences, between Apple and Google’s approach to mobile and desktop convergence.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jun 2018 22:06:10 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/06/11/wwwcomputerworldcom-also-takes.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/06/12/wwwcomputerworldcom-also-takes.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;It strikes me that &lt;a href=&quot;https://mondaynote.com/ios-macos-what-no-actually-means-90b9fb2c46c7&quot;&gt;Apple’s plans for running iOS apps on MacOS&lt;/a&gt; looks very similar to Google’s running Android apps on ChromeOS. &lt;a href=&quot;https://developer.android.com/topic/arc/input-compatibility&quot;&gt;Google is providing for mouse support in Android apps&lt;/a&gt;, which makes me wonder why Apple couldn’t add mouse support to iOS on iPads? There isn’t sa technical reason, I suspect it’s all about preserving Macs, assuming lack of mouse support in iOS is strong impediment to using iOS for productivity work.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jun 2018 10:37:33 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/06/11/it-strikes-me.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/06/11/it-strikes-me.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I wish there was such a thing as insertion point actions on my personal devices, here is what I mean. If I am adding a task in &lt;a href=&quot;https://noteplan.co/&quot;&gt;Noteplan&lt;/a&gt; on my iPad to call a friend, it would be really cool to just tap and hold, to get an Actions menu, from which I see an option that says “Add link to a contact.”  A link would be pasted at the current location of the cursor.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jun 2018 11:10:29 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/06/08/i-wish-there.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/06/08/i-wish-there.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.theverge.com/circuitbreaker/2018/6/5/17429662/google-project-oasis-terrarium-weather-conditions&quot;&gt;Project Oasis&lt;/a&gt; looks cool. Thinking about trying it out.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jun 2018 18:30:23 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/06/07/project-oasis-looks.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/06/07/project-oasis-looks.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I like Drafts, but I think the concept behind it is nonsensical. The idea of Drafts is that you use it to write and edit any text that you can then send to other apps, which also have the capability to write and edit text. So, you see “actions” in Drafts for entering tasks in apps like OmniFocus and Todoist, but why is that easier than just entering information in Microblog, OmniFocus and Todoist? It seems to me that people who use iOS for productivity are so enamored by the workflows they have created they don’t seem to realize the workflows are basically workarounds for deficiencies that existed in previous versions of iOS.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am finding the number of iOS apps that basically do the same thing insane! Really, how many markdown editors are needed?&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jun 2018 10:33:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/06/07/i-like-drafts.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/06/07/i-like-drafts.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I haven’t seen much written about this, but &lt;a href=&quot;https://developer.apple.com/videos/play/wwdc2018/211/&quot;&gt;it looks to me like Siri Shortcuts is the new Workflow&lt;/a&gt;. Will Workflow as we now know it go away to be replaced by the Siri Shortcuts app? It’s ironic that Apple aquired an app, Workflow, to make another app it aquired, Siri, more useful.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jun 2018 16:20:25 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/06/06/i-havent-seen.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/06/06/i-havent-seen.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://realpersonalcomputing.com/2018/06/06/the-pad-quill-ipad-pro-105-oxford-case/&quot;&gt;The Pad and Quill iPad Pro 10.5 Oxford Case&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ve written and published my first blog post with images entirely on my iPad.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jun 2018 13:27:54 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/06/06/the-pad-quill.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/06/06/the-pad-quill.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I want iOS Do Not Disturb while I am using the Kindle app. I should be able to create this capability using Workflow, but Apple doesn’t let third party apps tinker with such settings.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jun 2018 12:50:08 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/06/06/i-want-ios.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/06/06/i-want-ios.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;It appears as though everyone that I follow is at WWDC&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jun 2018 14:32:09 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/06/04/it-appears-as.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/06/04/it-appears-as.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Gradually, the sun sets&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://frankmcpherson.blog/uploads/2018/efffcef8e9.jpg&quot; width=&quot;600&quot; height=&quot;600&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jun 2018 22:11:05 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/06/03/gradually-the-sun.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/06/04/gradually-the-sun.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;That feeling the last night of vacation.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jun 2018 22:07:48 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/06/03/that-feeling-the.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/06/04/that-feeling-the.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I find really frustrating how inconsistent sharing works across apps with iOS. Try sharing a web page to Drafts or micro.blog and you end up with different results. Why?&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jun 2018 12:38:54 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/06/02/i-find-really.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/06/02/i-find-really.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ohmypizza.com/2018/06/ipad-needs-to-grow-up.php&quot;&gt;ohmypizza.com: The iPad Needs To Grow Up&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My one request of Apple is to add mouse support to the iPad. Apple can look at how Windows and Android handle mouse support on touchscreens, it can’t be that hard.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jun 2018 12:37:22 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/06/02/ohmypizzacom-the-ipad.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/06/02/ohmypizzacom-the-ipad.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Back at one of my favorite places.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://frankmcpherson.blog/uploads/2018/d9248bf21e.jpg&quot; width=&quot;600&quot; height=&quot;600&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jun 2018 17:22:59 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/06/01/back-at-one.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/06/01/back-at-one.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;The biggest ethical topic of our time might be that just because we &lt;strong&gt;can&lt;/strong&gt; do something &lt;strong&gt;doesn’t mean we should do it.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 30 May 2018 22:47:16 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/05/30/the-biggest-ethical.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/05/31/the-biggest-ethical.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I think the root of &lt;a href=&quot;https://the-narthex.org/2018/05/30/the-importance-of-god-theology/&quot;&gt;bad theology &lt;/a&gt; is the focus on the problem, sin, rather than on how things are supposed to be, oneness. If sin is separation from God, then racism is really the modern label for original sin. We are all connected and we are meant to see ourselves as connected to each other and God.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 30 May 2018 13:36:26 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/05/30/173626.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/05/30/173626.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Right now it takes way too much work for me to share pictures on micro.blog because I use an Android phone. I take the picture using my phone, which is stored in Google Photos, then open the picture on my iPad, download it, then open the micro.blog app and add the picture to a post like this one.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://frankmcpherson.blog/uploads/2018/ed77d36315.jpg&quot; width=&quot;600&quot; height=&quot;600&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 29 May 2018 22:44:58 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/05/29/right-now-it.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/05/30/right-now-it.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Today I read &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.macstories.net/reviews/agenda-for-ios-review/&quot;&gt;a review&lt;/a&gt; about an app called &lt;a href=&quot;https://agenda.com/&quot;&gt;Agenda&lt;/a&gt; that shared a name with a Personal Information Manager (PIM) that I liked back in the day called &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Lotus_Agenda&quot;&gt;Lotus Agenda&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 29 May 2018 22:12:51 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/05/29/today-i-read.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/05/30/today-i-read.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;IPad+Lightening Digital AV adapter+HDMI cable+MLB At Bat app = watching the Cubs on the hotel room TV.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 29 May 2018 20:19:54 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/05/29/ipadlightening-digital-av.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/05/30/ipadlightening-digital-av.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <title>Tolerance Is Fundamental To Freedom</title>
        
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Tolerance is fundamental to freedom. If we stop tolerating actions or opinions that we disagree with, you stop freedom, democracy disappears and is replaced by dictatorship. The irony is for the idea that kneeling during the national anthem is disrespectful and should not be tolerated, we are giving up the very freedom that too many gave their lives for.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can not dictate respect. Dictating respect is counter to tolerance and is counterproductive because respect is earned, not given.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do you really want freedom? If you do, it starts by tolerating those with whom you disagree and not treating them with contempt.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 29 May 2018 12:53:21 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/05/29/tolerance-is-fundamental.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/05/29/tolerance-is-fundamental.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;“This is ultimately the most important distinction between platforms and aggregators: platforms are powerful because they facilitate a relationship between 3rd-party suppliers and end users; aggregators, on the other hand, intermediate and control it.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://stratechery.com/2018/the-bill-gates-line/&quot;&gt;The Bill Gates Line&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do all platforms ultimately end up being commoditized? I see companies like Google and Facebook striving to not be like the personal computer or Windows, so I suspect they choose to be aggregators to protect themselves.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 29 May 2018 11:29:12 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/05/29/this-is-ultimately.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/05/29/this-is-ultimately.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://gr36.com/2017-01-19-bear-app-review/&quot;&gt;gr36.com Review of Bear&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am surprised that few, if any, reviews of notes apps like Bear don’t address security.  Can you encrypt the content you put in the app? How easy is that encryption? Can you encrypt entire notes? Notebooks? Or just snippets of text? And who holds the keys?&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 29 May 2018 11:18:59 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/05/29/grcom-review-of.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/05/29/grcom-review-of.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;My first criteria for staying at a hotel is a comfortable bed. My second is a restaurant or bar in or near the hotel.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://frankmcpherson.blog/uploads/2018/8d3cc0083c.jpg&quot; width=&quot;600&quot; height=&quot;600&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 28 May 2018 11:25:25 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/05/28/my-first-criteria.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/05/28/my-first-criteria.html</guid>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
