<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Frank McPherson's Web Notes</title>
    <description>Follow &lt;a href=&quot;https://micro.blog/frankm&quot;&gt;@frankm on Micro.blog&lt;/a&gt;.</description>
    <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/</link>
    <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jul 2018 19:25:43 -0400</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 Jul 2018 19:25:43 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.engadget.com/2018/07/25/android-p-final-preview-release/&quot;&gt;Android P’s final test release is here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Google has released the final public beta for Android P, so I have decided to install it on my Pixel 2. I’ve enabled the gesture navigation and so far everything works great and the phone seems faster.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jul 2018 19:25:30 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/07/25/android-ps-final.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/07/25/android-ps-final.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.slashgear.com/keep-your-iphone-or-galaxy-note-ipad-best-tablet-android-guide-23538525/&quot;&gt;I agree with Slashgear&lt;/a&gt; that users ought to be looking at lower cost tablets over more expensive smartphones. The majority of my personal computing is done on a tablet, either an iPad Mini or an iPad Pro. I use my smartphone when when I don’t have my tablet or in location where using a tablet is not practical.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jul 2018 10:56:58 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/07/24/i-agree-with.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/07/24/i-agree-with.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.costco.com/Microsoft-Surface-Go-Bundle---Intel-Pentium---1800-x-1200-Display---Windows-10-in-S-Mode---Surface-Type-Cover.product.100428070.html&quot;&gt;A Costco bundle like this&lt;/a&gt; is how I purchased my Surface 3.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If I didn’t own the iPad Pro 10.5 I would probably be all over the Surface Pro Go.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jul 2018 10:45:37 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/07/24/a-costco-bundle.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/07/24/a-costco-bundle.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Trumps tax cuts &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bloomberg.com/view/articles/2018-07-18/trump-s-tax-cut-hasn-t-done-anything-for-workers&quot;&gt;are not cutting it&lt;/a&gt;. The idea of cutting taxes will result in more jobs and higher wages is a myth. Corporations are hyper-optimized for shareholder return, which is done by cutting jobs and maintaining or lowering wages.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In almost all areas in the United States, mistakes are being made on the fundamentals. If the premise upon which a decision is based is wrong, then the decision and its consequences are wrong.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The foundation is cracking, and nobody is willing to face up to this reality.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jul 2018 10:42:22 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/07/24/trumps-tax-cuts.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/07/24/trumps-tax-cuts.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;While I am at it, despite that I use &lt;a href=&quot;https://micro.blog&quot;&gt;micro.blog&lt;/a&gt;, I have to confess that I don’t “get” micro.blogs. Perhaps I am being too literal. To me, a blog, is a blog, but there are titleless posts and posts with titles. Blogging back in 1999 was oriented around dates, and a weblog was a log of what one saw and reacted to on the web on a particular date. (In otherwords, titleless posts.)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now, I do get the idea of &lt;a href=&quot;https://kfitz.info/feeds-and-gardens/&quot;&gt;coherent interaction relating to a blog post&lt;/a&gt; that is probably the real, special sauce, to micro.blog. Back in 1999 we tried to implement this concept through link backs, but that had the challenge of notification of when someone did a link back so that you can participate in the “conversation.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://indieweb.org/Webmention&quot;&gt;Webmentions&lt;/a&gt; may be a better technlogical implementation of the link back concept. Ironic that the micro.blog blog doesn’t seem to support it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Again, being honest, I don’t write what I write on my blogs for the comments or the likes or the shares. I selfishly write for me, and if you the reader get value out of what I write, all the better.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jul 2018 09:04:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/07/24/while-i-am.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/07/24/while-i-am.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I guess that I am getting old, I don’t get microcasts. For my ears, podcasts can be too long AND too short. Something that you say in two minutes can be written. Printed words, on the web, is the primary way I consume information. Audio adds anothe format requiring additional hardware. I recognize that I may be exhibiting how I have been programmed by media companies all these years.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jul 2018 08:47:54 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/07/24/i-guess-that.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/07/24/i-guess-that.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;POTUS is &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.seattletimes.com/nation-world/bidenrsquos-corvette-fact-is-nations-leaders-not-allowed-to-drive/&quot;&gt;not allowed to drive a car&lt;/a&gt;. I am beginning to think POTUS should not be allowed to use social networks either. Congress could pass a law. Do we really want to end up in a war because of a tweet?&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jul 2018 15:29:21 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/07/23/potus-is-not.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/07/23/potus-is-not.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I did not know that &lt;a href=&quot;https://frankmcpherson.blog&quot;&gt;my micro.blog site&lt;/a&gt; is actually &lt;a href=&quot;http://manton.org/2016/07/06/building-on-jekyll.html&quot;&gt;based on Jekyll&lt;/a&gt;, but it makes sense given that I can get a copy stored on Github.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jul 2018 15:00:39 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/07/23/190039.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/07/23/190039.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;What bothers me more is the number of people who find &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/jeffjarvis/status/1021334339399843840&quot;&gt;the president’s behavior&lt;/a&gt; acceptable. We have a huge disconnect in what is acceptable competency of a U.S. President. I want a person who can kill thousands on my behalf to be competent. For too many competency was not at all important in deciding between Clinton and Trump.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jul 2018 09:50:34 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/07/23/what-bothers-me.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/07/23/what-bothers-me.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;American Christianity is as much an oxymoron as Roman Catholicism.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 22 Jul 2018 12:23:01 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/07/22/american-christianity-is.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/07/22/american-christianity-is.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://archive.org/stream/byte-magazine-1983-01/1983_01_BYTE_08-01_Looking_Ahead#page/n373/mode/1up&quot;&gt;Review of the Timex Sinclair 1000&lt;/a&gt; in the January 1983 issue of Byte magazine.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jul 2018 17:14:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/07/21/review-of-the.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/07/21/review-of-the.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;If you were a teenager in the 80s and did anything with a computer, you probably coveted Compute! Now you can &lt;a href=&quot;https://archive.org/details/compute-magazine&quot;&gt;go back in time and browse through old issues&lt;/a&gt; thanks to the Internet Archive.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jul 2018 13:19:31 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/07/21/if-you-were.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/07/21/if-you-were.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;My first computer was the &lt;a href=&quot;http://oldcomputers.net/ts1000.html&quot;&gt;Timex Sinclair&lt;/a&gt; 1000 that my grandmother gave me as a birthday present in 1983. I got that computer because it was cheap enough for my grandmother to buy, and she somehow determined back then that computers where the future.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One of the unique things about the TS1000 is that it had a membrane keyboard and each key had multiple functions, most notably certain function key combinations produced BASIC reserve words geared towards making it easy to learn how to program. The TS1000’s keyboard could be seen today as a predecessor to today’s on-screen keyboards.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Back in the 80s and early 90s all personal computers came with an operating system and the BASIC programming language. While you could buy some pre-packaged software, the most common way to add programs to a computer was by either writing yourself or by typing one that was &lt;a href=&quot;https://arstechnica.com/staff/2012/12/first-encounter-compute-magazine-and-its-glorious-tedious-type-in-code/&quot;&gt;printed in a magazine&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The TS1000 was an educational computer and the forefather to the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.raspberrypi.org/&quot;&gt;Raspberry Pi&lt;/a&gt; that you can buy today for as little as $30. I have several Raspberry Pis that I tinker with, and I think parents ought to buy them for any child who is at all interested in studying computers.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jul 2018 13:14:21 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/07/21/my-first-computer.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/07/21/my-first-computer.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;What scares me most is that Trump supporters do not appear to have lines, by which I mean there is nothing Trump can do that will lose their support. Ought right determination to not change one’s mind, no matter what is frightening. Progress requires an openness to admitting that one is wrong.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jul 2018 11:39:25 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/07/21/153925.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/07/21/153925.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.slashgear.com/buffy-the-vampire-slayer-reboot-revealed-with-joss-whedon-onboard-20538369/&quot;&gt;Buffy The Vampire Slayer reboot revealed with Joss Whedon onboard - SlashGear&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have mixed feeling about this news. As time has past I have accepted the series is done and moved on. In some ways it would be nice to leave it be. On the other hand, knowing Joss is behind this has me curious to see where he takes the story. I think Joss is smart enough to know a reboot cannot try to be the same. In the meantime, lots can happen for this to not happen.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jul 2018 11:31:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/07/21/buffy-the-vampire.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/07/21/buffy-the-vampire.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I find the renewed interest in RSS interesting and refreshing.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jul 2018 11:19:37 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/07/21/i-find-the.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/07/21/i-find-the.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Pro tip: during a rain storm the best indoor place to hear the rain fall is an attached garage, assuming it is not insulated. An attic may be as good, but mine isn’t accessible. I stood in my garage for several minutes this morning listening to the rain.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jul 2018 10:30:12 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/07/21/pro-tip-during.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/07/21/pro-tip-during.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;What is &lt;a href=&quot;https://solid.mit.edu/&quot;&gt;Solid&lt;/a&gt;?&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jul 2018 15:00:43 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/07/20/what-is-solid.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/07/20/what-is-solid.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I recently rewrote &lt;a href=&quot;https://frankm.org&quot;&gt;my profile page&lt;/a&gt; and implemented HTTPS using Amazon S3 and Cloudfront.  In my opinion S3 provides one of the easiest and least expensive ways to host a simple, static web site. Unfortunately HTTPS adds complexity, both in what you need to do to build the site and also in how you maintain it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I did a brief survey and I think that that the simplest way to set up a web site with HTTPS is to host with a service like &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bluehost.com&quot;&gt;Bluehost&lt;/a&gt;, which provides a free SSL certificate. &lt;a href=&quot;https://my.bluehost.com/hosting/help/141#shared&quot;&gt;Bluehosts’s $8.99/month price&lt;/a&gt; is reasonable, but not as cheap as Amazon for a really small site like mine, which is a single HTML page.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, in my opinion with the current push to HTTPS,  you are better off going with a service provider that includes HTTPS as part of the service. If you are more technical and willing to fiddle with things, you can save money with S3/Cloudfront.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jul 2018 14:50:42 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/07/20/i-recently-rewrote.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/07/20/i-recently-rewrote.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;You can &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.troyhunt.com/everything-you-need-to-know-about-loading-a-free-lets-encrypt-certificate-into-an-azure-website/&quot;&gt;use Let’s Encrypt with Azure&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jul 2018 10:42:46 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/07/20/you-can-use.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/07/20/you-can-use.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/app-service/app-service-web-get-started-html&quot;&gt;Azure has a different approach to static sites&lt;/a&gt; because it associates a VM to the site rather than storage. The big difference is that you can’t associate a custom domain to the free tier, you will have to pay for the VM and it looks like you will need to buy a certificate. The upside to this approach is that you can implement SSL without having to use a CDN.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jul 2018 10:28:08 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/07/20/azure-has-a.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/07/20/azure-has-a.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://cloud.google.com/storage/docs/hosting-static-website&quot;&gt;Google’s static website hosting&lt;/a&gt; is pretty much the same as AWS, and it also requires using a CDN if you want to implement HTTPS.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jul 2018 10:21:24 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/07/20/googles-static-website.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/07/20/googles-static-website.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://scripting.com/2018/07/17.html#a135225&quot;&gt;Dave Winer picks up on a point&lt;/a&gt; that &lt;a href=&quot;http://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/07/16/i-dont-find.html&quot;&gt;I wrote about yesterday&lt;/a&gt;. Trump’s behavior regarding Putin and Russia is driven by money and ego.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jul 2018 11:45:05 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/07/17/dave-winer-picks.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/07/17/dave-winer-picks.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;When I first saw the title of this book, &lt;a href=&quot;http://howtothinkbook.com/&quot;&gt;How to Think&lt;/a&gt;, my reaction was, “do we really need to teach people how to think?” Then I thought, yes, yes we do! More thinking and less reacting is needed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;From the author:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;“Eventually two points occurred to me. The first is that many of our fiercest disputes occur because the people involved simply aren’t thinking: they’re reacting or emoting or virtue-signaling or ingroup-identifying. The second is that I have spent my entire career thinking and trying to teach others to think.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jul 2018 11:32:35 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/07/17/153235.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/07/17/153235.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;The yellow represents a severe thunderstorm warning. The blue pin is my house, and immediately below is the rest of our condo complex. If I walked 5 minutes out my front door I would be out of the warned area.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://frankmcpherson.blog/uploads/2018/8378076369.jpg&quot; width=&quot;600&quot; height=&quot;600&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jul 2018 16:12:33 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/07/16/the-yellow-represents.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/07/16/the-yellow-represents.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I don’t find it &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cnn.com/2018/07/16/politics/donald-trump-vladimir-putin-press-conference/index.html&quot;&gt;shocking&lt;/a&gt; that Trump has a very favorable view towards Putin and Russia. Russia is about the only place that will give Trump a loan. Putin has not personally offended Trump in any way, and Trump likely does admire what Putin has.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All Putin has to do is continue stroking Trump’s ego.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jul 2018 15:52:10 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/07/16/i-dont-find.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/07/16/i-dont-find.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/tpn/pdfs&quot;&gt;Here is an incredible catalog&lt;/a&gt; of 1,000 technical-oriented PDFs hosted on Github.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jul 2018 15:14:48 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/07/16/here-is-an.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/07/16/here-is-an.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Despite what you might hear about one person or another having “all the qualifications” to be a Supreme Court Justice, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.history.com/news/7-things-you-might-not-know-about-the-u-s-supreme-court&quot;&gt;there are actually no constitutional qualifications&lt;/a&gt; for a Supreme Court Justice.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When someone says a person is qualified, what they really mean is that they think that person agrees with their ideology.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jul 2018 09:12:08 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/07/16/despite-what-you.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/07/16/despite-what-you.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;My latest theological essay: &lt;a href=&quot;https://writing.frankmcpherson.net/theology/2018/07/15/thy-kingdom-come,-my-kingdom-go.html&quot;&gt;Thy Kingdom Come, My Kingdom Go&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jul 2018 20:33:55 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/07/15/my-latest-theological.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/07/16/my-latest-theological.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://kottke.org/18/07/the-story-of-the-last-survivor-of-the-atlantic-slave-trade&quot;&gt;The story of the last survivor of the Atlantic slave trade&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jul 2018 13:03:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/07/15/the-story-of.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/07/15/the-story-of.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Interesting story about &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.strongtowns.org/journal/2018/7/9/evolution-of-the-corner-store&quot;&gt;corner stores&lt;/a&gt;. When I was growing up the nearest grocery store, one of these corner stores, was DeRidders. In the late 70s a fire gutted the building and the owner built a &lt;a href=&quot;https://goo.gl/maps/uGbj5AdMq6K2&quot;&gt;much smaller “party” store across the U.S. highway from the old site&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In its day DeRidders was one of maybe a half dozen grocery stores in my small home town. Four were located on the three quarter mile long Main Street. Today only one grocery store remains in my home town, and it competes with a Walmart Superstore ten miles away.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jul 2018 00:45:46 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/07/15/interesting-story-about.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/07/15/interesting-story-about.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.msn.com/en-us/money/news/the-last-sears-in-chicago-is-closing/ar-AAzRFpI&quot;&gt;The last Sears store in Chicago&lt;/a&gt; is closing today. Sears has been in Chicago since 1887.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jul 2018 00:24:53 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/07/15/the-last-sears.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/07/15/the-last-sears.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;A couple of six pointers strolled through our back yard, nibbling on trees along the way.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://frankmcpherson.blog/uploads/2018/d20aea9e8f.jpg&quot; width=&quot;600&quot; height=&quot;600&quot; /&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://frankmcpherson.blog/uploads/2018/e70c4bd3df.jpg&quot; width=&quot;600&quot; height=&quot;600&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 14 Jul 2018 23:06:45 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/07/14/a-couple-of.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/07/15/a-couple-of.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I have updated &lt;a href=&quot;https://frankm.org/&quot;&gt;my profile page&lt;/a&gt; and learned something about content delivery networks along the way. I host my profile in a S3 bucket that I have now configured for HTTPS. The only way to use Amazon’s SSL certificate is by using their CDN, Cloudfront.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The fun begins when you make changes to said web page and they never seem to appear, even though you know for certain the latest version of that page is in the bucket. Turns out you need to invalidate that page in the Cloudfront console to force it to be refreshed in the cache. Along the way I made changes to the TTL for the page.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All fun geeky stuff, but really too many hoops to serve a simple web page with one picture.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 14 Jul 2018 23:02:13 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/07/14/i-have-updated.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/07/15/i-have-updated.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.ayjay.org/the-world-of-the-deal/&quot;&gt;Alan Jacobs:&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;In Trump’s world, you fit into one of three categories. You may be a mark, you may be leverage, you may be a loser.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 14 Jul 2018 14:12:25 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/07/14/alan-jacobs-in.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/07/14/alan-jacobs-in.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://bostonreview.net/archives/BR30.2/raboteau.php&quot;&gt;bostonreview.net&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;At its best, democracy balances the rights of the individual with the responsibility to participate in the public conversations and tasks that make civic community possible. However, the possibility of so stressing rights that we forget responsibility is a perennial threat to American liberty. The choice of privileging one over the other comes down to a simple, but profound question: “What is freedom for?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 14 Jul 2018 13:57:29 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/07/14/bostonreviewnet-at-its.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/07/14/bostonreviewnet-at-its.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Remember when Wimbledon was for the serve and volley? Watching Serena complain about the bad bounces coming from the chewed up grass and dirt in the baseline has me thinking, get up the court toward the net where the grass is greener. Not to mention a volley eliminates the bad bounce.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 14 Jul 2018 12:13:18 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/07/14/remember-when-wimbledon.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/07/14/remember-when-wimbledon.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Watching tennis in HD has me wondering how I could have done so on a 19 inch set while growing up. Like playing tennis with a wood racquet.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 14 Jul 2018 11:48:16 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/07/14/watching-tennis-in.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/07/14/watching-tennis-in.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;According to &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.informationclearinghouse.info/article41086.htm&quot;&gt;this site&lt;/a&gt; the United States has NOT been at war only 5 of my 52 years. Throughout its existence the United States has been at war 93% of the time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Christian nation? Not according to Jesus.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jul 2018 15:24:53 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/07/11/according-to-this.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/07/11/according-to-this.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;On the gripping hand, in a year the price of &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.laptopmag.com/articles/microsoft-surface-go-specs-price&quot;&gt;the Surface Go&lt;/a&gt; may become low enough to make it a worthwhile replacement of my Surface 3. The Surface 3 is my only personally-owned Windows 10 machine.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For me, the main problem with the Go is its price, I think Microsoft either needs to bundle the keyboard or drop the price down at least $100. What makes the Go appealing is the built-in kickstand and mouse support, both of which are things I miss using the iPad Pro.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jul 2018 14:42:25 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/07/10/on-the-gripping.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/07/10/on-the-gripping.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.wired.com/story/surface-go-microsofts-big-bet-on-a-tiny-computer-future/&quot;&gt;Surface Go Is Microsoft’s Big Bet on a Tiny-Computer Future&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am curious to see how much smaller the Surface Go is compared to the Surface 3. Unfortunately for Microsoft, I’ve replaced the Surface 3 with a iPad Pro 10.5 and it is hard to see why I would want the new Go rather than the iPad.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jul 2018 22:25:41 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/07/09/surface-go-is.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/07/10/surface-go-is.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I really dislike &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cnet.com/news/starbucks-will-ditch-plastic-straws-for-fancy-designer-lids/#ftag=CAD590a51e&quot;&gt;these new lids&lt;/a&gt; that Starbucks is starting to use.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jul 2018 11:47:36 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/07/09/i-really-dislike.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/07/09/i-really-dislike.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I am running the iOS 12 beta in my iPad Mini and therefore need to learn the &lt;a href=&quot;https://lifehacker.com/the-iphone-x-gestures-you-should-master-1821395834&quot;&gt;iPhone X gestures&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jul 2018 11:41:32 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/07/09/i-am-running.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/07/09/i-am-running.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Do the ends justify the means?&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 07 Jul 2018 16:05:17 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/07/07/do-the-ends.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/07/07/do-the-ends.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;The backup of this site in GitHub has refreshed, and that repo has been pulled down to my iPad. Backup of backup&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jul 2018 14:36:10 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/07/06/the-backup-of.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/07/06/the-backup-of.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/Lisa-Shearin/e/B001JSEICI&quot;&gt;Lisa Shearin&lt;/a&gt; is one of my favorite authors. Settling in with &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/gp/product/198682490X/ref=as_li_qf_asin_il_tl?ie=UTF8&amp;amp;tag=lisashearin-20&amp;amp;creative=9325&amp;amp;linkCode=as2&amp;amp;creativeASIN=198682490X&amp;amp;linkId=10fc01c6e671b7f2529d1ac6769df1c2&quot;&gt;her latest&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jul 2018 11:14:04 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/07/06/lisa-shearin-is.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/07/06/lisa-shearin-is.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Moved to the patio. May be here most of the day. #staycation&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://frankmcpherson.blog/uploads/2018/30b7c7dbc6.jpg&quot; width=&quot;600&quot; height=&quot;600&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jul 2018 11:07:15 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/07/06/moved-to-the.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/07/06/moved-to-the.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;What the heck?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://frankmcpherson.blog/uploads/2018/1ae6dc703c.jpg&quot; width=&quot;600&quot; height=&quot;600&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jul 2018 18:53:55 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/07/05/what-the-heck.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/07/05/what-the-heck.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://frankmcpherson.blog/uploads/2018/d8e258211b.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;My office for the afternoon&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I work from home, I vocation in Starbucks.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jul 2018 17:26:55 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/07/05/i-work-from.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/07/05/i-work-from.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Today I wrote a &lt;a href=&quot;https://writing.frankmcpherson.net/ipad/2018/07/05/using-noteplan-to-manage-personal-projects.html&quot;&gt;new article&lt;/a&gt; on my site hosted by Netlify that includes an image that I have stored in a S3 bucket. The bucket is not set up for HTTPS. Netlify has sent me an email that mixed, insecure content has been detected on my blog.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sigh. Now I have to go and figure out how get that bucket, which is hosting my &lt;a href=&quot;http://frankm.org&quot;&gt;personal profile&lt;/a&gt; set up with HTTPS. Fortunately, it is a simple bucket, but really, this whole ham-handed push to HTTPS is getting old, fast.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jul 2018 17:14:40 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/07/05/today-i-wrote.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/07/05/today-i-wrote.html</guid>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
