<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Frank McPherson</title>
    <description>Follow &lt;a href=&quot;https://micro.blog/frankm&quot;&gt;@frankm on Micro.blog&lt;/a&gt;.</description>
    <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/</link>
    <pubDate>Sun, 24 Jun 2018 15:08:11 -0400</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 24 Jun 2018 15:08:11 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Do you think of micro.blog as a blog or an alternative to Twitter?&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 24 Jun 2018 15:07:29 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/06/24/do-you-think.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/06/24/do-you-think.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Greatness is neither self determined nor self declared.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jun 2018 10:36:13 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/06/21/greatness-is-neither.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/06/21/greatness-is-neither.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I’ve got Android Messages for Web enabled and I found that it does work with Chrome on iOS, however I haven’t received notifications for new in-bound messages on iOS. You can also set up Messages for Web with multiple computers but only one can be active at a time. I have to admit, this seems to work pretty well and helps me get past a limitation with Pushbullet on iOS.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jun 2018 17:53:22 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/06/20/ive-got-android.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/06/20/ive-got-android.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;If we can’t agree that there are things humans should not do to other humans, particularly to those who are vulnerable, then we have a problem and that is being exposed in the United States’ &lt;a href=&quot;https://slate.com/news-and-politics/2018/06/how-the-trump-administration-is-defending-its-indefensible-child-separation-policy.html&quot;&gt;current practice of separating children from families&lt;/a&gt;. From the time that Trump seriously started running for president we have seen a widening gulf between those who care about what we do to one another and those who do not.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jun 2018 09:20:40 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/06/20/if-we-cant.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/06/20/if-we-cant.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I don’t get the need for &lt;a href=&quot;https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.google.android.apps.podcasts&quot;&gt;Google Podcasts&lt;/a&gt;. There is already a section for Podcasts in Google Play Music that I have been using and have subscriptions. Google Podcasts isn’t even smart enough to import my existing subscriptions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don’t listen to many podcasts any more now that I don’t spend an hour a day in the car commuting to an office.  In fact, most of my recent podcast listening has been using Apple’s Podcast app on an iPad.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jun 2018 14:18:33 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/06/19/i-dont-get.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/06/19/i-dont-get.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I am curious to know whether &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.zdnet.com/article/googles-android-messages-for-web-is-here-this-is-how-it-lets-you-text-from-pcs-macs&quot;&gt;the new web messenging feature of Android Messages&lt;/a&gt; will work in a browser on an iPad. I’ve been using Pushbullet for this type of remote texting, and that works well from an Android tablet or Windows PC, but the iOS version of Pushbullet does not support SMS.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jun 2018 14:08:19 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/06/19/i-am-curious.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/06/19/i-am-curious.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I’ve been hanging out at the new Starbucks down the road from my house.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://frankmcpherson.blog/uploads/2018/9069db1e4a.jpg&quot; width=&quot;600&quot; height=&quot;599&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 16 Jun 2018 17:00:09 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/06/16/ive-been-hanging.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/06/16/ive-been-hanging.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I think I know what happened. With previous posts I published from Ulysses I did not enable markdown in the publishing dialog and therefore the publisher converted the markdown to HTML so it appeared correct in Wordpress. In the previous post I enabled markdown, and since Wordpress was not configured to use markdown it did not render properly. So, to have enabled markdown in the writing settings of the WP-Admin console, which fixed the problem.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In other words…. operator error! :)&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 16 Jun 2018 15:59:22 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/06/16/195922.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/06/16/195922.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I just published &lt;a href=&quot;https://the-narthex.org/2018/06/16/daryl-madden-unlearn/&quot;&gt;a post on one of my Wordpress blogs&lt;/a&gt; using Ulysses for iOS, which I have used to publish before, and for some reason the markdown for hyperlinks was not properly recognized. Does anyone know if something has changed with Wordpress?&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 16 Jun 2018 15:37:11 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/06/16/i-just-published.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/06/16/i-just-published.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;It is really disappointing that Apple removed all handwriting recognition keyboards for iOS. I would really like to be able to use the Apple Pencil in all of apps, which I should be able to at least do with a HWR keyboard. It looks like MyScript Stack and Stylus were all removed from the store.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jun 2018 10:02:21 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/06/15/140221.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/06/15/140221.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <title>The Overthrow Will Not Be By Force.</title>
        
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Too many people in the United States think our government will be overthrown by force when the reality is it is happening in just the opposite manner. The strong arguments against gun control in the U.S. is evidence of this, as the argument centers around needing to keep guns as protection against government oppression. The powers that be don’t need to take guns away, they just need us to keep arguing about them, which fossilizes idealogy and keeps attention away from what is really happening.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The constitution enables authoritarianism when Congress and the Supreme Court do not function in their jobs as overseers of the Presidency. When Congress and the Supreme Court simply align with a president due to party affliation, you have a dictator in practice.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today the process nearly complete, and gerrymandering will seal the deal. Gerrymandering removes the one power citizens have, which is to vote. You don’t need to burn down the flag nor rip up the Constitution, all that is needed is idealogical compliance to what the Presidency wants.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jun 2018 11:01:33 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/06/13/the-overthrow-will.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/06/13/the-overthrow-will.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.computerworld.com/article/3278560/mobile-apps/ios-apps-on-mac.html&quot;&gt;www.computerworld.com&lt;/a&gt; also takes note of the similarities, and differences, between Apple and Google’s approach to mobile and desktop convergence.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jun 2018 22:06:10 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/06/11/wwwcomputerworldcom-also-takes.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/06/12/wwwcomputerworldcom-also-takes.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;It strikes me that &lt;a href=&quot;https://mondaynote.com/ios-macos-what-no-actually-means-90b9fb2c46c7&quot;&gt;Apple’s plans for running iOS apps on MacOS&lt;/a&gt; looks very similar to Google’s running Android apps on ChromeOS. &lt;a href=&quot;https://developer.android.com/topic/arc/input-compatibility&quot;&gt;Google is providing for mouse support in Android apps&lt;/a&gt;, which makes me wonder why Apple couldn’t add mouse support to iOS on iPads? There isn’t sa technical reason, I suspect it’s all about preserving Macs, assuming lack of mouse support in iOS is strong impediment to using iOS for productivity work.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jun 2018 10:37:33 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/06/11/it-strikes-me.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/06/11/it-strikes-me.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I wish there was such a thing as insertion point actions on my personal devices, here is what I mean. If I am adding a task in &lt;a href=&quot;https://noteplan.co/&quot;&gt;Noteplan&lt;/a&gt; on my iPad to call a friend, it would be really cool to just tap and hold, to get an Actions menu, from which I see an option that says “Add link to a contact.”  A link would be pasted at the current location of the cursor.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jun 2018 11:10:29 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/06/08/i-wish-there.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/06/08/i-wish-there.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.theverge.com/circuitbreaker/2018/6/5/17429662/google-project-oasis-terrarium-weather-conditions&quot;&gt;Project Oasis&lt;/a&gt; looks cool. Thinking about trying it out.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jun 2018 18:30:23 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/06/07/project-oasis-looks.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/06/07/project-oasis-looks.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I like Drafts, but I think the concept behind it is nonsensical. The idea of Drafts is that you use it to write and edit any text that you can then send to other apps, which also have the capability to write and edit text. So, you see “actions” in Drafts for entering tasks in apps like OmniFocus and Todoist, but why is that easier than just entering information in Microblog, OmniFocus and Todoist? It seems to me that people who use iOS for productivity are so enamored by the workflows they have created they don’t seem to realize the workflows are basically workarounds for deficiencies that existed in previous versions of iOS.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am finding the number of iOS apps that basically do the same thing insane! Really, how many markdown editors are needed?&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jun 2018 10:33:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/06/07/i-like-drafts.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/06/07/i-like-drafts.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I haven’t seen much written about this, but &lt;a href=&quot;https://developer.apple.com/videos/play/wwdc2018/211/&quot;&gt;it looks to me like Siri Shortcuts is the new Workflow&lt;/a&gt;. Will Workflow as we now know it go away to be replaced by the Siri Shortcuts app? It’s ironic that Apple aquired an app, Workflow, to make another app it aquired, Siri, more useful.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jun 2018 16:20:25 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/06/06/i-havent-seen.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/06/06/i-havent-seen.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://realpersonalcomputing.com/2018/06/06/the-pad-quill-ipad-pro-105-oxford-case/&quot;&gt;The Pad and Quill iPad Pro 10.5 Oxford Case&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ve written and published my first blog post with images entirely on my iPad.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jun 2018 13:27:54 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/06/06/the-pad-quill.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/06/06/the-pad-quill.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I want iOS Do Not Disturb while I am using the Kindle app. I should be able to create this capability using Workflow, but Apple doesn’t let third party apps tinker with such settings.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jun 2018 12:50:08 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/06/06/i-want-ios.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/06/06/i-want-ios.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;It appears as though everyone that I follow is at WWDC&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jun 2018 14:32:09 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/06/04/it-appears-as.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/06/04/it-appears-as.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Gradually, the sun sets&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://frankmcpherson.blog/uploads/2018/efffcef8e9.jpg&quot; width=&quot;600&quot; height=&quot;600&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jun 2018 22:11:05 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/06/03/gradually-the-sun.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/06/04/gradually-the-sun.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;That feeling the last night of vacation.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jun 2018 22:07:48 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/06/03/that-feeling-the.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/06/04/that-feeling-the.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I find really frustrating how inconsistent sharing works across apps with iOS. Try sharing a web page to Drafts or micro.blog and you end up with different results. Why?&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jun 2018 12:38:54 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/06/02/i-find-really.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/06/02/i-find-really.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://ohmypizza.com/2018/06/ipad-needs-to-grow-up.php&quot;&gt;ohmypizza.com: The iPad Needs To Grow Up&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My one request of Apple is to add mouse support to the iPad. Apple can look at how Windows and Android handle mouse support on touchscreens, it can’t be that hard.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jun 2018 12:37:22 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/06/02/ohmypizzacom-the-ipad.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/06/02/ohmypizzacom-the-ipad.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Back at one of my favorite places.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://frankmcpherson.blog/uploads/2018/d9248bf21e.jpg&quot; width=&quot;600&quot; height=&quot;600&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jun 2018 17:22:59 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/06/01/back-at-one.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/06/01/back-at-one.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;The biggest ethical topic of our time might be that just because we &lt;strong&gt;can&lt;/strong&gt; do something &lt;strong&gt;doesn’t mean we should do it.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 30 May 2018 22:47:16 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/05/30/the-biggest-ethical.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/05/31/the-biggest-ethical.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I think the root of &lt;a href=&quot;https://the-narthex.org/2018/05/30/the-importance-of-god-theology/&quot;&gt;bad theology &lt;/a&gt; is the focus on the problem, sin, rather than on how things are supposed to be, oneness. If sin is separation from God, then racism is really the modern label for original sin. We are all connected and we are meant to see ourselves as connected to each other and God.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 30 May 2018 13:36:26 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/05/30/173626.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/05/30/173626.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Right now it takes way too much work for me to share pictures on micro.blog because I use an Android phone. I take the picture using my phone, which is stored in Google Photos, then open the picture on my iPad, download it, then open the micro.blog app and add the picture to a post like this one.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://frankmcpherson.blog/uploads/2018/ed77d36315.jpg&quot; width=&quot;600&quot; height=&quot;600&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 29 May 2018 22:44:58 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/05/29/right-now-it.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/05/30/right-now-it.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Today I read &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.macstories.net/reviews/agenda-for-ios-review/&quot;&gt;a review&lt;/a&gt; about an app called &lt;a href=&quot;https://agenda.com/&quot;&gt;Agenda&lt;/a&gt; that shared a name with a Personal Information Manager (PIM) that I liked back in the day called &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Lotus_Agenda&quot;&gt;Lotus Agenda&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 29 May 2018 22:12:51 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/05/29/today-i-read.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/05/30/today-i-read.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;IPad+Lightening Digital AV adapter+HDMI cable+MLB At Bat app = watching the Cubs on the hotel room TV.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 29 May 2018 20:19:54 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/05/29/ipadlightening-digital-av.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/05/30/ipadlightening-digital-av.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <title>Tolerance Is Fundamental To Freedom</title>
        
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Tolerance is fundamental to freedom. If we stop tolerating actions or opinions that we disagree with, you stop freedom, democracy disappears and is replaced by dictatorship. The irony is for the idea that kneeling during the national anthem is disrespectful and should not be tolerated, we are giving up the very freedom that too many gave their lives for.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can not dictate respect. Dictating respect is counter to tolerance and is counterproductive because respect is earned, not given.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do you really want freedom? If you do, it starts by tolerating those with whom you disagree and not treating them with contempt.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 29 May 2018 12:53:21 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/05/29/tolerance-is-fundamental.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/05/29/tolerance-is-fundamental.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;“This is ultimately the most important distinction between platforms and aggregators: platforms are powerful because they facilitate a relationship between 3rd-party suppliers and end users; aggregators, on the other hand, intermediate and control it.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://stratechery.com/2018/the-bill-gates-line/&quot;&gt;The Bill Gates Line&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do all platforms ultimately end up being commoditized? I see companies like Google and Facebook striving to not be like the personal computer or Windows, so I suspect they choose to be aggregators to protect themselves.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 29 May 2018 11:29:12 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/05/29/this-is-ultimately.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/05/29/this-is-ultimately.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://gr36.com/2017-01-19-bear-app-review/&quot;&gt;gr36.com Review of Bear&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am surprised that few, if any, reviews of notes apps like Bear don’t address security.  Can you encrypt the content you put in the app? How easy is that encryption? Can you encrypt entire notes? Notebooks? Or just snippets of text? And who holds the keys?&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 29 May 2018 11:18:59 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/05/29/grcom-review-of.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/05/29/grcom-review-of.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;My first criteria for staying at a hotel is a comfortable bed. My second is a restaurant or bar in or near the hotel.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://frankmcpherson.blog/uploads/2018/8d3cc0083c.jpg&quot; width=&quot;600&quot; height=&quot;600&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 28 May 2018 11:25:25 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/05/28/my-first-criteria.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/05/28/my-first-criteria.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I would like a Firefox extension that takes grabs the title of a web page and the URL of that web page, puts that into a Markdown link format and stores to the clipboard for pasting into the micro.blog web input box. In the past I have used applets for linking to web pages in my blog posts.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 24 May 2018 09:47:03 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/05/24/i-would-like.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/05/24/i-would-like.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://chromeunboxed.com/news/acer-launches-four-chromebooks-kaby-lake-spin&quot;&gt;Acer Debuts Four New Chromebooks&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am thinking if Chromebook manufacturers expect people to be using Linux apps, wouldn’t they provide storage options greater than 64 GB? I find the news about Linux support on Chromebooks intriguing enough for me to consider purchasing a new one once the feature is widely available.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 24 May 2018 09:44:31 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/05/24/acer-debuts-four.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/05/24/acer-debuts-four.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://sports.yahoo.com/trump-nfl-protesters-maybe-shouldnt-country-114402328.html&quot;&gt;Trump on NFL protesters: ‘Maybe you shouldn’t be in the country’&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a democracy the leader does not dictate behavior, that is called dictatorship. The fact that Trump does not get the fundamentals of democracy is scary, and the fact that we elected such a person President is very disappointing. The fact that so many people do not see this as an issue is frightening, and a sign that our democracy may already be lost.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 24 May 2018 09:27:43 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/05/24/trump-on-nfl.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/05/24/trump-on-nfl.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;From the flowering tree in our back yard.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://frankmcpherson.blog/uploads/2018/c72bc366bf.jpg&quot; width=&quot;600&quot; height=&quot;600&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 21 May 2018 20:59:08 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/05/21/from-the-flowering.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/05/22/from-the-flowering.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;For the last couple of weeks I have been using &lt;a href=&quot;https://noteplan.co/&quot;&gt;NotePlan&lt;/a&gt;, and I think what I like most about it is that you end up with a daily log of what you did. &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.foldingtext.com/&quot;&gt;FoldingText&lt;/a&gt; looks like a similarly useful tool, but not available on iOS, but I like outliners. The feature I want in an outliner is simple linking both with an outline file and to external items.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 19 May 2018 10:25:01 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/05/19/for-the-last.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/05/19/for-the-last.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;The best thing about micro.blog is that it’s just people. When you browse through Discover, you are discovering people.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 19 May 2018 10:09:44 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/05/19/the-best-thing.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/05/19/the-best-thing.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;It seems to me that the majority of school shootings have occurred at public schools. Am I wrong?&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 18 May 2018 14:53:38 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/05/18/it-seems-to.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/05/18/it-seems-to.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Because I am an introvert, emotionally-charged meetings, even if I am not the target of the emotion, is very draining. Today was one of those days, being remedied by guacamole and a &lt;a href=&quot;https://foundersbrewing.com/our-beer/dankwood/&quot;&gt;Dankwood&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 17 May 2018 20:11:11 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/05/17/because-i-am.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/05/18/because-i-am.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;One of the most surprising things I’ve learned about myself during the last three years is that I like guacamole.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 17 May 2018 19:56:52 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/05/17/235652.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/05/17/235652.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;The Cubs lost another game to the Braves. The Braves look for real.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 16 May 2018 22:31:22 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/05/16/the-cubs-lost.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/05/17/the-cubs-lost.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Is there a way to disable iOS predictive text when using an external keyboard?&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 14 May 2018 09:05:47 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/05/14/130547.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/05/14/130547.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Chrome OS’ forthcoming &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.xda-developers.com/linux-apps-chrome-os-overview-crostini/&quot;&gt;ability to run Linux apps&lt;/a&gt; appears to me to mostly be something Google did so that their engineers could actually use the Pixelbook. Once that feature is seen in the code you might as well let the broad developer community in on the fun.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The question is whether regular users will benefit from this feature. Most likely not if nothing more than the actual number of Linux apps a “regular user” might find useful are limited. Right now I can only think one app I will want to run in such a container and that is &lt;a href=&quot;https://standardnotes.org&quot;&gt;Standard Notes&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 13 May 2018 13:05:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/05/13/chrome-os-forthcoming.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/05/13/chrome-os-forthcoming.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;My Fossil Q Explorist now talks.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 13 May 2018 12:54:51 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/05/13/my-fossil-q.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/05/13/my-fossil-q.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;A credit card company &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.theverge.com/2018/3/6/17071478/spam-calls-how-to-stop-block-robocalls-robots-scam-iphone-android&quot;&gt;robot keeps calling my smart phone&lt;/a&gt; and neither Google nor &lt;a href=&quot;https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.nomorobo&amp;amp;hl=en_US&quot;&gt;Nomorobo&lt;/a&gt; is able to catch it because each call is from a different number and often local. Right now, if caller ID doesn’t show something I recognize, I don’t answer the phone.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I personally think we need to outlaw phone calling robots, before &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.theverge.com/2018/5/9/17335710/google-duplex-phone-call-ai-assistant-service-industry&quot;&gt;Google Duplex&lt;/a&gt; gets entrenched.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 May 2018 12:03:45 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/05/10/a-credit-card.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/05/10/a-credit-card.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.theverge.com/2018/5/8/17333154/googe-lens-ai-ar-live-demo-hands-on-io-2018&quot;&gt;Google Lens actually shows how AI can make life easier - The Verge&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I just would like Lens to tell me what type of bird I took a picture of in Bermuda.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 08 May 2018 21:33:46 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/05/08/google-lens-actually.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/05/09/google-lens-actually.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Do we want our devices to become nannies? I get why Google and Microsoft are reacting to reports on the addictive nature of the devices, but it seems to me we need to learn self control and not rely on external influence to tell us what and what not to do.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 08 May 2018 20:08:38 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/05/08/do-we-want.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/05/09/do-we-want.html</guid>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
