<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Frank McPherson's Web Notes</title>
    <description>Follow &lt;a href=&quot;https://micro.blog/frankm&quot;&gt;@frankm on Micro.blog&lt;/a&gt;.</description>
    <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/</link>
    <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jul 2018 11:04:55 -0400</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 30 Jul 2018 11:04:55 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;One reaction to &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cnbc.com/2018/07/10/eu-hits-alphabet-google-with-android-antitrust-fine.html&quot;&gt;the EU decision regarding Android&lt;/a&gt; is that Google may have erred by making Android open source. A close source Android likely would have been bad for consumers and have prevented it from being as widely used as it is. We would likely be dealing with more than two defacto mobile OS standards.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, is &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2018-07-19/google-team-is-said-to-plot-android-successor-draw-skepticism&quot;&gt;Fuchsia the solution to Googles Android EU problem&lt;/a&gt;?&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jul 2018 11:04:41 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/07/30/one-reaction-to.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/07/30/one-reaction-to.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Which is more important, what you spend your time doing or who you spend your time with?&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jul 2018 11:26:03 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/07/28/which-is-more.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/07/28/which-is-more.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I’ve been running &lt;a href=&quot;https://android-developers.googleblog.com/2018/07/final-preview-update-official-android-p.html&quot;&gt;Android P&lt;/a&gt; on my Pixel 2 for 24 hours and so far have seen no problems and I do believe the phone runs faster than when running Oreo.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2018 17:33:21 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/07/26/ive-been-running.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/07/26/ive-been-running.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Here is something that I find ironic. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.wired.com/story/google-chrome-https-not-secure-label/&quot;&gt;Google is taking the lead&lt;/a&gt; towards pushing all web hosting on the Internet to use HTTPS. I have a blog that is hosted on Blogger, which is owned by Google. You can only &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.tech2watch.info/&quot;&gt;access that blog by HTTP&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.tech2watch.info&quot;&gt;HTTPS does not work&lt;/a&gt; automatically as it does Wordpress and many other blog hosting sites.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2018 11:12:54 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/07/26/here-is-something.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/07/26/here-is-something.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Nothing threatens individual freedom and the meaning of life like war, poverty, terror. But there are also indirect and only slightly more remote dangers. One of these is the stupefaction of man . . . by mass culture with its intentional or commercially motivated lowering of intellectual level and content, with its stress on entertainment or utilitarianism, and with its carefully protective censorship. – &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.newyorker.com/news/our-columnists/fifty-years-later-andrei-sakharovs-most-famous-essay-is-a-powerful-model-of-writing-for-social-change&quot;&gt;Andrei Sakharov&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The New Yorker article I link to above that includes the quote above is very good, recommended.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2018 11:02:53 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/07/26/nothing-threatens-individual.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/07/26/nothing-threatens-individual.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;One thing lacking is discourse and the desire to find lasting solutions to problems. There is a difference in a dogmatic view to problems, by which I mean a view in which solutions are pre-determined and implemented no matter what, and a scientific view that &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.newyorker.com/news/our-columnists/fifty-years-later-andrei-sakharovs-most-famous-essay-is-a-powerful-model-of-writing-for-social-change&quot;&gt;presents ideas&lt;/a&gt; (hypothesis) that are proven not to be false.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The key element to an hypothesis, or an idea, is the opennes to it being wrong.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2018 09:17:09 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/07/26/one-thing-lacking.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/07/26/one-thing-lacking.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I am now deep in beta land with the iOS 12 beta on my iPad Mini and Android P on my Pixel.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jul 2018 19:30:19 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/07/25/i-am-now.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/07/25/i-am-now.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.engadget.com/2018/07/25/android-p-final-preview-release/&quot;&gt;Android P’s final test release is here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Google has released the final public beta for Android P, so I have decided to install it on my Pixel 2. I’ve enabled the gesture navigation and so far everything works great and the phone seems faster.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jul 2018 19:25:30 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/07/25/android-ps-final.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/07/25/android-ps-final.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.slashgear.com/keep-your-iphone-or-galaxy-note-ipad-best-tablet-android-guide-23538525/&quot;&gt;I agree with Slashgear&lt;/a&gt; that users ought to be looking at lower cost tablets over more expensive smartphones. The majority of my personal computing is done on a tablet, either an iPad Mini or an iPad Pro. I use my smartphone when when I don’t have my tablet or in location where using a tablet is not practical.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jul 2018 10:56:58 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/07/24/i-agree-with.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/07/24/i-agree-with.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.costco.com/Microsoft-Surface-Go-Bundle---Intel-Pentium---1800-x-1200-Display---Windows-10-in-S-Mode---Surface-Type-Cover.product.100428070.html&quot;&gt;A Costco bundle like this&lt;/a&gt; is how I purchased my Surface 3.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If I didn’t own the iPad Pro 10.5 I would probably be all over the Surface Pro Go.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jul 2018 10:45:37 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/07/24/a-costco-bundle.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/07/24/a-costco-bundle.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Trumps tax cuts &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bloomberg.com/view/articles/2018-07-18/trump-s-tax-cut-hasn-t-done-anything-for-workers&quot;&gt;are not cutting it&lt;/a&gt;. The idea of cutting taxes will result in more jobs and higher wages is a myth. Corporations are hyper-optimized for shareholder return, which is done by cutting jobs and maintaining or lowering wages.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In almost all areas in the United States, mistakes are being made on the fundamentals. If the premise upon which a decision is based is wrong, then the decision and its consequences are wrong.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The foundation is cracking, and nobody is willing to face up to this reality.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jul 2018 10:42:22 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/07/24/trumps-tax-cuts.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/07/24/trumps-tax-cuts.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;While I am at it, despite that I use &lt;a href=&quot;https://micro.blog&quot;&gt;micro.blog&lt;/a&gt;, I have to confess that I don’t “get” micro.blogs. Perhaps I am being too literal. To me, a blog, is a blog, but there are titleless posts and posts with titles. Blogging back in 1999 was oriented around dates, and a weblog was a log of what one saw and reacted to on the web on a particular date. (In otherwords, titleless posts.)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now, I do get the idea of &lt;a href=&quot;https://kfitz.info/feeds-and-gardens/&quot;&gt;coherent interaction relating to a blog post&lt;/a&gt; that is probably the real, special sauce, to micro.blog. Back in 1999 we tried to implement this concept through link backs, but that had the challenge of notification of when someone did a link back so that you can participate in the “conversation.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://indieweb.org/Webmention&quot;&gt;Webmentions&lt;/a&gt; may be a better technlogical implementation of the link back concept. Ironic that the micro.blog blog doesn’t seem to support it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Again, being honest, I don’t write what I write on my blogs for the comments or the likes or the shares. I selfishly write for me, and if you the reader get value out of what I write, all the better.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jul 2018 09:04:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/07/24/while-i-am.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/07/24/while-i-am.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I guess that I am getting old, I don’t get microcasts. For my ears, podcasts can be too long AND too short. Something that you say in two minutes can be written. Printed words, on the web, is the primary way I consume information. Audio adds anothe format requiring additional hardware. I recognize that I may be exhibiting how I have been programmed by media companies all these years.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jul 2018 08:47:54 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/07/24/i-guess-that.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/07/24/i-guess-that.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;POTUS is &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.seattletimes.com/nation-world/bidenrsquos-corvette-fact-is-nations-leaders-not-allowed-to-drive/&quot;&gt;not allowed to drive a car&lt;/a&gt;. I am beginning to think POTUS should not be allowed to use social networks either. Congress could pass a law. Do we really want to end up in a war because of a tweet?&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jul 2018 15:29:21 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/07/23/potus-is-not.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/07/23/potus-is-not.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I did not know that &lt;a href=&quot;https://frankmcpherson.blog&quot;&gt;my micro.blog site&lt;/a&gt; is actually &lt;a href=&quot;http://manton.org/2016/07/06/building-on-jekyll.html&quot;&gt;based on Jekyll&lt;/a&gt;, but it makes sense given that I can get a copy stored on Github.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jul 2018 15:00:39 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/07/23/190039.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/07/23/190039.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;What bothers me more is the number of people who find &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/jeffjarvis/status/1021334339399843840&quot;&gt;the president’s behavior&lt;/a&gt; acceptable. We have a huge disconnect in what is acceptable competency of a U.S. President. I want a person who can kill thousands on my behalf to be competent. For too many competency was not at all important in deciding between Clinton and Trump.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jul 2018 09:50:34 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/07/23/what-bothers-me.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/07/23/what-bothers-me.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;American Christianity is as much an oxymoron as Roman Catholicism.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 22 Jul 2018 12:23:01 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/07/22/american-christianity-is.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/07/22/american-christianity-is.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://archive.org/stream/byte-magazine-1983-01/1983_01_BYTE_08-01_Looking_Ahead#page/n373/mode/1up&quot;&gt;Review of the Timex Sinclair 1000&lt;/a&gt; in the January 1983 issue of Byte magazine.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jul 2018 17:14:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/07/21/review-of-the.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/07/21/review-of-the.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;If you were a teenager in the 80s and did anything with a computer, you probably coveted Compute! Now you can &lt;a href=&quot;https://archive.org/details/compute-magazine&quot;&gt;go back in time and browse through old issues&lt;/a&gt; thanks to the Internet Archive.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jul 2018 13:19:31 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/07/21/if-you-were.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/07/21/if-you-were.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;My first computer was the &lt;a href=&quot;http://oldcomputers.net/ts1000.html&quot;&gt;Timex Sinclair&lt;/a&gt; 1000 that my grandmother gave me as a birthday present in 1983. I got that computer because it was cheap enough for my grandmother to buy, and she somehow determined back then that computers where the future.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One of the unique things about the TS1000 is that it had a membrane keyboard and each key had multiple functions, most notably certain function key combinations produced BASIC reserve words geared towards making it easy to learn how to program. The TS1000’s keyboard could be seen today as a predecessor to today’s on-screen keyboards.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Back in the 80s and early 90s all personal computers came with an operating system and the BASIC programming language. While you could buy some pre-packaged software, the most common way to add programs to a computer was by either writing yourself or by typing one that was &lt;a href=&quot;https://arstechnica.com/staff/2012/12/first-encounter-compute-magazine-and-its-glorious-tedious-type-in-code/&quot;&gt;printed in a magazine&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The TS1000 was an educational computer and the forefather to the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.raspberrypi.org/&quot;&gt;Raspberry Pi&lt;/a&gt; that you can buy today for as little as $30. I have several Raspberry Pis that I tinker with, and I think parents ought to buy them for any child who is at all interested in studying computers.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jul 2018 13:14:21 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/07/21/my-first-computer.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/07/21/my-first-computer.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;What scares me most is that Trump supporters do not appear to have lines, by which I mean there is nothing Trump can do that will lose their support. Ought right determination to not change one’s mind, no matter what is frightening. Progress requires an openness to admitting that one is wrong.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jul 2018 11:39:25 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/07/21/153925.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/07/21/153925.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.slashgear.com/buffy-the-vampire-slayer-reboot-revealed-with-joss-whedon-onboard-20538369/&quot;&gt;Buffy The Vampire Slayer reboot revealed with Joss Whedon onboard - SlashGear&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have mixed feeling about this news. As time has past I have accepted the series is done and moved on. In some ways it would be nice to leave it be. On the other hand, knowing Joss is behind this has me curious to see where he takes the story. I think Joss is smart enough to know a reboot cannot try to be the same. In the meantime, lots can happen for this to not happen.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jul 2018 11:31:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/07/21/buffy-the-vampire.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/07/21/buffy-the-vampire.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I find the renewed interest in RSS interesting and refreshing.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jul 2018 11:19:37 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/07/21/i-find-the.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/07/21/i-find-the.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Pro tip: during a rain storm the best indoor place to hear the rain fall is an attached garage, assuming it is not insulated. An attic may be as good, but mine isn’t accessible. I stood in my garage for several minutes this morning listening to the rain.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jul 2018 10:30:12 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/07/21/pro-tip-during.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/07/21/pro-tip-during.html</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
      	
        <description>&lt;p&gt;What is &lt;a href=&quot;https://solid.mit.edu/&quot;&gt;Solid&lt;/a&gt;?&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jul 2018 15:00:43 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://frankmcpherson.blog/2018/07/20/what-is-solid.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://frankm.micro.blog/2018/07/20/what-is-solid.html</guid>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
